<AppUpdater>
  <update>
    <latestVersion>2.7.3</latestVersion>
    <url>https://dl-xda.xposed.info/modules/kmod.xposed_v2730_a6f585.apk</url>
    <en>
- Added swipe option to reply messages (from WhatsApp 2.18.282).
- Now with the option not to show updates when there is an update, the update toast will be displayed only twice, and not every time you enter WhatsApp.
- Fixed bug with background colors which show black color by default.
- Other bugs fixed.
    </en>
    <ar>
- خيار التمرير السريع للرد على الرسائل (من WhatsApp 2.18.282).
- الآن مع خيار عدم عرض التحديثات ، عندما يكون هناك تحديث ، سيتم عرض نخب التحديث مرتين فقط ، وليس كل مرة تدخل فيها WhatsApp.
- إصلاح الخلل مع لون الخلفيات التي تظهر بشكل افتراضي باللون الأسود.
- تم تصحيح الأخطاء الأخرى.
    </ar>
    <bn>
- বার্তা উত্তর করার জন্য যোগ করা সোয়াপ বিকল্প (হোয়াটসঅ্যাপ থেকে 2.18.282).
- এখন আপডেট আপডেট না দেখানোর সাথে, যখন একটি আপডেট থাকে, আপডেট টোস্ট কেবলমাত্র দুবার প্রদর্শিত হবে এবং প্রতিবারই আপনি হোয়াটসঅ্যাপে প্রবেশ করবেন না।
- ডিফল্ট রং কালো দেখানো যা ব্যাকগ্রাউন্ড রং সঙ্গে বাগ সংশোধন করা হয়েছে
- অন্যান্য ত্রুটি সংশোধন করা হয়েছে।
    </bn>
    <de>
- Wischoptionen zum beantworten von Nachrichten hinzugefügt (von WhatsApp 2.18.282 an).
- Mit der Option Aktualisierungen nicht anzuzeigen, wenn eine Aktualisierung vorhanden ist, werden Aktualisierungsbenachrichtigungen nun nur noch zweimal angezeigt und nicht jedes mal wenn du WhatsApp öffnest.
- Fehler mit Hintergrundfarben, die Schwarz als Standard anzeigen, behoben
- Andere Fehler behoben.
	</de>
    <es>
- Se agregó la opción deslizar para responder mensajes (de WhatsApp 2.18.282).
- Ahora con la opción de no mostrar actualizaciones, cuando hay una actualización, el Toast de actualización se mostrará solo dos veces, y no cada vez que ingrese a WhatsApp.
- Se corrigió el error con el color de los fondos que mostraba por defecto el color negro.
- Otros errores fueron corregidos.
    </es>
    <fr>
- Ajout de l'option swipe pour répondre aux messages (à partir de WhatsApp 2.18.282).
- Maintenant, avec l'option de ne pas afficher les mises à jour, lorsqu'il y a une mise à jour, le toast de mise à jour ne sera affiché que deux fois, et pas à chaque fois que vous entrez dans WhatsApp.
- Correction du bug avec la couleur des arrière-plans qui montraient par défaut la couleur noire.
- Les autres erreurs ont été corrigées.
    </fr>
    <hi>
- संदेशों का जवाब देने के लिए स्वाइप विकल्प जोड़ा गया (व्हाट्सएप 2.18.282 से).
- अब अद्यतन दिखाने के विकल्प के साथ, जब कोई अपडेट होता है, तो अद्यतन टोस्ट केवल दो बार प्रदर्शित किया जाएगा, और जब भी आप व्हाट्सएप दर्ज नहीं करेंगे।
- पृष्ठभूमि के रंग के साथ बग फिक्स्ड जो डिफ़ॉल्ट रूप से रंग काला दिखाया गया है।
- अन्य त्रुटियों को सही किया गया था।
    </hi>
	<in>
- Ditambahkan opsi swipe untuk membalas pesan (dari WhatsApp 2.18.282).
- Sekarang dengan opsi untuk tidak menampilkan pembaruan, ketika ada pembaruan, toast pembaruan akan ditampilkan hanya dua kali, dan tidak setiap kali Anda memasukkan WhatsApp.
- Memperbaiki bug dengan warna latar belakang yang ditunjukkan secara default warna hitam.
- Kesalahan lainnya diperbaiki.
	</in>
    <it>
- Aggiunta l'opzione per rispondere ai messaggi con uno swipe (da WhatsApp 2.18.282).
- Ora con l'opzione di non mostrare gli aggiornamenti, quando c'è un aggiornamento, il messaggio di aggiornamento verrà visualizzato solo due volte, e non ogni volta che si entra in WhatsApp.
- Corretto il bug con il colore degli sfondi che mostrava di default il colore nero.
- Correzione di altri errori.
    </it>
    <nl>
- Toegevoegd swipe optie om berichten te beantwoorden (van WhatsApp 2.18.282).
- Nu met de optie om geen updates te tonen, zal bij een update de update-toast slechts tweemaal worden getoond en niet elke keer dat je WhatsApp invoert.
- Probleem opgelost met de kleur van de achtergronden die standaard de kleur zwart laat zien.
- Andere fouten zijn gecorrigeerd.
    </nl>	
    <pt>
- Adicionada a opção de fazer swipe para responder mensagens (do WhatsApp 2.18.282).
- Agora com a opção de não mostrar atualizações, quando houver uma atualização, uma toast será exibida apenas duas vezes em que o WhatsApp for aberto.
- Corrigido o bug na opção de cor dos fundos, onde era mostrado por padrão a cor preta.
- Outros erros foram corrigidos.
    </pt>
	<ro>
- A fost adăugată opțiunea de glisare pentru a răspunde la mesaje (de la WhatsApp 2.18.282).
- Acum, cu opțiunea de a nu afișa actualizări, atunci când există o actualizare, toastul de actualizare va fi afișat numai de două ori și nu de fiecare dată când introduceți WhatsApp.
- S-a rezolvat problema cu culoarea fundalului afișată în mod implicit culoarea neagră.
- Alte erori au fost corectate.
	</ro>
    <ru>
- Добавлена возможность прокрутки для ответа на сообщения (из WhatsApp 2.18.282).
- Теперь с возможностью не показывать обновления, когда есть обновление, тост обновления будет отображаться только дважды, и не каждый раз, когда вы вводите WhatsApp.
- Исправлена ошибка с цветом фона, отображаемым по умолчанию цветом черного цвета.
- Исправлены другие ошибки.
    </ru>
    <tr>
- Mesajları cevaplamaz için kaydırma özelliği eklendi (WhatsApp 2.118.282'den).
- Güncelleştirmeleri göstermeme seçeneği ile birlikte artık, güncelleştirme olduğunda, güncelleştirme toast'ı her WhatsApp'a girişinizde değil, sadece iki kez gösterilecek. 
- Varsayılan olarak siyah renkle gösterilen arka planların rengi ile ilgili hata düzeltildi.
- Diğer hatalar düzeltildi.
    </tr>
  </update>
</AppUpdater>
