<AppUpdater>
  <update>
    <latestVersion>2.5.1</latestVersion>
    <url>http://dl-xda.xposed.info/modules/kmod.xposed_v2_a69ec6.apk</url>
    <en>
- Now, when you save a theme, the privacy settings will not be saved to the theme.
- You can now hide your status online, in the WhatsApp widget or in the main screen of the module (it is configured in the privacy section).
- Security warning bubbles are now the same as custom bubbles (dates and warnings).
- Now the corners that are shown in the bubbles, when a link or a quote is displayed, are no longer displayed.
- Added GIF finder (2.16.353+) and server selector (2.16.356+).
- Added option to activate video call.
- Added option to hide the contact photo and groups.
- Moved text from Responder, from "Text left side" to "Text Central" section in the conversations section.
- Now when you press the apply changes button, a dialog box is displayed while applying the changes.
- Added Arabic language.
- Fixed the problem that forced closing when you entered KMod from WhatsApp.
- Corrections for the latest beta versions of Google Play.
- Other corrections of errors.
    </en>
	<ar>
-الان عندما تحفظ الثيم لن يتم حفظ اعدادات الخصوصية معه
-الان يمكنك ان تخفي حالة متصل الان من ويدجيت الوتساب او من الشاشة الرئيسية في kmod ( انها موجودة في قسم الخصوصية )
-فقاعات التنبيهات ستكون نفس فقاعات التواريخ
-الان لن يتم اظهار الزوايا عندما يعرض رابط او ينقل تعليق
-اضافة موجد الصور المتحركة gif +2.16.353 والسيرفر المخدم +2.16.356 
-اضافة خيار لتفعيل مكالمات الفديو
-اضافة خيار لاخفاء صورة البروفايل والجروبات
-يتم تغيير النص من قسم النص الايسر والنص المركزي من قسم المحادثات
-الان عندما تضغط زر تطبيق التغييرات سيظهر صندوق نص اثناء تطبيق التغييرات
-اضافة اللغة العربية
-اصلاح مشكلة الاغلاق القسري اثناء الانتقال لل kmod من الوتساب
-اصدارات احدث اصدارات بيتا من جوجل بلاي
-اصلاحات اخطاء اخرى
	</ar>
    <bn>
- এখন, আপনি যখন একটি থিম সংরক্ষণ, গোপনীয়তা সেটিংস থিম সংরক্ষণ করা হবে না.
- আপনি এখন হোয়াটসঅ্যাপ উইজেট থেকে অনলাইন আপনার অবস্থা লুকিয়ে রাখতে পারেন, বা মডিউল প্রধান পর্দা থেকে (এটা গোপনীয়তা অধ্যায় থেকে কনফিগার করা).
- নিরাপত্তা সতর্কতা বুদবুদ এখন কাস্টম বুদবুদ (তারিখ ও ভীতি প্রদর্শনকরী হিসাবে) হিসাবে একই.
- এখন কোণে যে, বুদবুদ দেখানো হয় যখন একটি লিঙ্ক প্রদর্শন করা হয় বা একটি মন্তব্য উদ্ধৃত করা হয়, প্রদর্শন এখন আর নেই.
- GIF আবিষ্কর্তা (2.16.353+) এবং সার্ভার নির্বাচক (2.16.356+) যোগ করা হয়েছে.
- ভিডিও কল সক্রিয় করার বিকল্প যোগ করা হয়েছে.
- যোগাযোগ ফটো এবং গ্রুপ লুকাতে বিকল্প যোগ করা হয়েছে.
- প্রতিক্রিয়াকারী থেকে টেক্সট পরিবর্তন হয়েছে, অধ্যায় "পাঠ্য বাম পাশ" থেকে "টেক্সট সেন্ট্রাল" কথোপকথন বিভাগে থেকে.
- এখন যখন আপনি আবেদন পরিবর্তন করুন বাটনটি ক্লিক করুন, একটি ডায়লগ বক্স যখন পরিবর্তনগুলি প্রয়োগ প্রদর্শন করা হয়.
- যোগ করা হয়েছে আরবি ভাষা.
- সমস্যা যে ক্লোজিং বাধ্য যখন আপনি হোয়াটসঅ্যাপ থেকে kmod প্রবেশ সংশোধন করা হয়েছে.
- গুগল এর সর্বশেষ বিটা সংস্করণ জন্য সংশোধণী খেলুন.
- ত্রুটি অন্যান্য সংশোধন.
    </bn>
    <de>
- Wenn du nun ein Thema speicherst, werden Privatsphäre Einstellungen nicht im Thema gespeichert.
- Du kannst nun deinen Online Status vom Widget oder dem Hauptbildschirm des Moduls aus verstecken (einstellbar in der Privatsphäre Sektion).
- Sicherheitswarnungsblasen sind nun die selben wie benutzerdefinierte Blasen (Daten und Warnungen).
- Die Ränder, die in Blasen angezeigt werden, wenn ein Link oder Zitat angezeigt wird, werden nun nicht länger angezeigt.
- GIF-Finder (2.16.353+) und Server Auswahl (2.16.356+) hinzugefügt.
- Option zum Video Anruf aktivieren hinzugefügt.
- Option zum verstecken von Kontakt und Gruppen Foto hinzugefügt
- Text vom Antwortsender von "Texte Links" nach "Zentraler Text" Sektion in der "Gespräche" Sektion verschoben.
- Wenn du nun auf die Änderungen anwenden Schaltfläche drückst, wird eine Dialog Box angezeigt während die Änderungen angewendet werden.
- Arabische Sprache hinzugefügt
- Problem gelöst, das zum erzwungenen Schließen führte, wenn man KMod von WhatsApp aus öffnete.
- Anpassung der letzten Beta Version des Google Playstore 
- Andere Korrekturen von Fehlern.
    </de>
    <es>
- Ahora, cuando guarde un tema, la configuración de privacidad no se guardará en éste.
- Ahora puedes ocultar tu estado de en línea, desde el widget de WhatsApp o desde la pantalla principal del módulo (se configura desde la sección de privacidad).
- Las burbujas de advertencia de seguridad son ahora las mismas que las burbujas personalizadas (fechas y advertencias).
- Ahora las esquinas que se muestran en las burbujas, cuando se muestra un enlace o se cita un comentario, ya no se muestran.
- Añadido buscador de gif (2.16.353+) y selector de servidor (2.16.356+).
- Añadida opción para activar videollamada.
- Añadida opción para ocultar la foto de contacto y grupos.
- Cambiado texto de Responder, de la sección de "Texto lado izquierdo" a "Texto central" en la sección de conversaciones.
- Ahora al pulsar el botón aplicar cambios, se muestra una ventana de dialogo mientras aplican los cambios.
- Añadido idioma Árabe.
- Solucionado el problema que forzaba cierre cuando entrabas a KMod desde WhatsApp.
- Correcciones para las últimas versiones beta de Google Play.
- Otras correcciones de errores.
    </es>
    <hi>
- अब, जब आप एक विषय बचाने के लिए, गोपनीयता सेटिंग्स विषय को बचाया नहीं किया जाएगा।
- अब आप WhatsApp विजेट से ऑनलाइन अपनी स्थिति को छुपा सकते हैं, या मॉड्यूल के मुख्य स्क्रीन से (यह गोपनीयता अनुभाग से कॉन्फ़िगर किया गया है)।
- सुरक्षा चेतावनी बुलबुले अब कस्टम बुलबुले (दिनांक और चेतावनी) के रूप में वही कर रहे हैं।
- अब कोनों कि, बुलबुले में दिखाया जाता है जब एक लिंक प्रदर्शित किया जाता है या एक टिप्पणी उद्धृत किया गया है, प्रदर्शित नहीं रह रहे हैं।
- GIF खोजक (2.16.353+) और सर्वर चयनकर्ता (2.16.356+) जोड़ा गया।
- वीडियो कॉल सक्रिय करने के लिए विकल्प जोड़ा गया।
- संपर्क फोटो और समूहों को छिपाने के लिए विकल्प जोड़ा गया।
- उत्तर से परिवर्तित पाठ, अनुभाग "पाठ बाएँ तरफ" के लिए "पाठ सेंट्रल" बातचीत अनुभाग में से।
- अब जब आप लागू परिवर्तन बटन दबाते हैं, एक संवाद बॉक्स जबकि परिवर्तनों को लागू करने प्रदर्शित किया जाता है।
- जोड़ा अरबी भाषा।
- समस्या यह है कि समापन मजबूर जब आप WhatsApp से kmod प्रवेश किया फिक्स्ड।
- समस्या तय है, जब अंतिम कनेक्शन छिपा हुआ था, ऑनलाइन हमेशा से था।
- गूगल के नवीनतम बीटा संस्करण के लिए सुधार खेलते हैं।
    </hi>
    <it>
- Ora, con il salvataggio di un tema, le opzioni privacy non verranno salvate con il tema. 
- È ora possibile nascondere lo status online dal widget di WhatsApp o dalla schermata principale del modulo (configurato dalla sezione privacy). 
- Le bolle di allerta sulla sicurezza sono ora uguali alle bolle custom (date e allerte). 
- Ora i bordi mostrati nelle bolle, quando un link è visualizzato o viene quotato un commento, non sono più visualizzate a lungo. 
- Aggiunta ricerca gif (2.16.353+) e selettore per il server (2.16.356+).
- Aggiunta opzione per attivare videochiamata. 
- Aggiunta opzione per nascondere la foto del contatto e dei gruppi. 
- Cambiato il testo dal Responder, dalla sezione "Testo lato sinistro" a "Testo Centrale" nella sezione delle conversazioni. 
- Ora quando viene premuto il tasto applica cambiamenti, una finestra di dialogo viene visualizzata durante l'attivazione dei cambiamenti. 
- Aggiunta lingua araba. 
- Sistemato il problema che provocava un arresto forzato in seguito all'ingresso in KMod da WhatsApp.
- Correzioni per le ultime versioni beta del Google Play. 
- Altre correzioni di errori.
    </it>
	<nl>
- Nu, als je het thema opslaat, de privé instellingen van het thema zullen niet worden opgeslagen. 
- Je kan nu je online status verbergen, vanuit de WhatsApp widget of het hoofd scherm van de module (het word geconfigureerd vanuit de privacy sectie). 
- Veiligheid waarschuwing ballonnen zijn nu hetzelfde als de gewone ballonnen (datums en waarschuwingen). 
- Nu zul je de hoeken van de ballonnen niet meer zien, als je een link ziet of als commentaar is gequote. 
- Gif zoeker toegevoegd (2.16.353+) en server kiezer (2.16.356+).
- Optie toegevoegd om video bellen te activeren. 
- Optie toegevoegd om contact en groeps foto te verbergen. 
- Tekst veranderd van ontvanger, van de sectie "Tekst linkerkant" naar "Tekst centraal" in de chat gesprekken sectie. 
- Als je nu op de knop veranderingen doorvoeren klikt, zal je een dialoog venster zien terwijl de veranderingen worden doorgevoerd. 
- Arabische taal toegevoegd. 
- Het probleem van geforceerd sluiten als je naar KMod wou gaan vanuit WhatsApp, is opgelost.
- Correcties voor de laatste beta versies van Google Play. 
- Andere fout correcties.
	</nl>	
    <pt>
- Agora, quando você salva um tema, as configurações de privacidade não serão salvas no tema.
- Agora você pode ocultar seu status on-line, no widget WhatsApp ou na tela principal do módulo (ele é configurado na seção de privacidade).
- As bolhas de aviso de segurança são agora as mesmas que as bolhas personalizadas (datas e avisos).
- Agora os cantos que são mostrados nas bolhas, quando um link ou uma citação é exibido, não são mais exibidos.
- Adicionado GIF finder (2.16.353+) e seletor de servidor (2.16.356+).
- Adicionado opção para ativar a chamada de vídeo.
- Adicionado opção para ocultar a foto de contato e grupos.
- Movido texto de Responder, de "Text left side" para "Text Central" seção na seção de conversas.
- Agora, quando você pressiona o botão aplicar alterações, uma caixa de diálogo é exibida durante a aplicação das alterações.
- Adicionado idioma árabe.
- Corrigido o problema que o fechamento forçado quando você digitou KMod do WhatsApp.
- Correções para as versões beta mais recentes do Google Play.
- Outras correcções de erros.
    </pt>
    <ru>
- Теперь, когда Вы сохраняете темы, настройки приватности не сохраняются к теме.
- Теперь вы можете скрывать свой статус онлайн, с виджета WhatsApp или с главного экрана модуля (он настраивается в разделе конфиденциальность).
- Пузырьки предупреждений системы безопасности теперь такие же, как и пользовательские пузыри (даты и предупреждений).
- Теперь уголки, которые показаны в пузырях, когда отображается ссылка или процитированный комментарий, больше не отображаются.
- Добавлен поиск GIF (2.16.353+) и выбор сервера (2.16.356+).
- Добавлена возможность активации видеосвязи.
- Добавлена опция для скрытия контактов, фото и групп.
- Изменен текст ответчика, "Текст слева" и "Центральный текст" в разделе беседы.
- Теперь, когда вы нажимаете кнопку "применить изменения", диалоговое окно отображается при внесении изменений.
- Добавлен Арабский язык.
- Исправлена проблема принудительного закрытия, когда вы вошли в KMod из WhatsApp.
- Исправления для последних бета-версий Google Play.
- Другие исправления ошибок.
    </ru>
    <tr>
- Artık bir temayı kayıt ettiğinizde, gizlilik ayarları tema ile birlikte kayıt edilmeyecek.
- Artık çevrimiçi durumunuzu Whatsapp widgetinden ya da modülün ana ekranından (gizlilik kısmından ayarlanıyor) değiştirebilirsiniz.
- Güvenlik uyarı balonları artık özel balonlarla aynı (tarih ve uyarılar).
- Balonların köşeleri, bir bağlantı görüntülendiğinde ya da mesaj cevaplandığında, artık gösterilmiyor.
- Gif arayıcı (2.16.353+) ve sunucu seçici (2.16.356+) eklendi.
- Görüntülü aramayı aktif etme seçeneği eklendi.
- Kişi fotoğraf ve gruplarını gizleme seçeneği eklendi.
- Mesajlaşma ekranındaki kişi ya da grup resimlerini gizleme eklendi.
- Artık ayarları uygula butonuna bastığınızda bir uyarı görüntüleniyor.
- Arapça eklendi.
- Kmod'a Whatsapp'tan girdiğinizde modülün çökmesine neden olan bir hata düzeltildi.
- Son Google play beta'sı için düzeltmeler yapıldı.
- Diğer hatalar düzeltildi.
    </tr>
  </update>
</AppUpdater>
