<AppUpdater>
  <update>
    <latestVersion>2.7.6</latestVersion>
    <url>https://dl-xda.xposed.info/modules/kmod.xposed_v2760_043c64.apk</url>
    <en>
- Added all privacy options again.
- Now you can add a button on the conversations screen to make phone calls.
- Restructured the icons section within the Conversations section.
- New method to update libraries (Hooks). They are now updated by selecting the Update libraries option, in the Updates section.
- Removed the Clear cache option in Settings (Now use the Update libraries option).
- Removed the automatic update of Hooks when entering WhatsApp (It didn't work correctly on some devices).
- Removed swipe to respond option (it's already active by default).
- Removed option to activate Stickers (it's already active by default).
- Removed option to replace the call button of WhatsApp by telephone calls (a separate button was added).
- Removed personalization of some screens of the Settings section (for now).
- Fixed other errors.
    </en>
    <ar>
- أضيفت جميع خيارات الخصوصية مرة أخرى.
- يمكنك الآن إضافة زر على شاشة المحادثات لإجراء مكالمات هاتفية.
- إعادة هيكلة قسم الرموز داخل قسم المحادثات.
- طريقة جديدة لتحديث المكتبات (السنانير). يتم تحديثها الآن عن طريق تحديد خيار تحديكتبات ، في قسم التحديثات.
- أزل خيار مسح ذاكرة التخزين المؤقت في الإعدادات (استخدم الآن خيار تحديث المكتبات).
- أزال التحديث التلقائي لـ Hooks عند دخول WhatsApp (لم ينجح بشكل صحيح في بعض الأجهزة).
- خيار السحب الذي تمت إزالته للرد (نشط بالفعل افتراضيًا).
- الخيار الذي تمت إزالته لتنشيط الملصقات (إنه نشط بالفعل افتراضيًا).
- الخيار الذي تمت إزالته لاستبدال زر الاتصال في WhatsApp عن طريق المكالمات الهاتفية (تمت إضافة زر منفصل).
- تمت إزالة التخصيص لبعض شاشات قسم الإعدادات (في الوقت الحالي).
- إصلاح الأخطاء الأخرى.
    </ar>
    <bn>
- সমস্ত গোপনীয়তার বিকল্প আবার যুক্ত।
- এখন আপনি ফোন কল করতে কথোপকথনের স্ক্রিনে একটি বোতাম যুক্ত করতে পারেন।
- কথোপকথন বিভাগের মধ্যে আইকন বিভাগ পুনর্গঠিত।
- লাইব্রেরি আপডেট করার নতুন পদ্ধতি (হুকস)। সেগুলি এখন আপডেট বিভাগে আপডেট লাইব্রেরি বিকল্পটি নির্বাচন করে আপডেট করা হয়।
- সেটিংসে সাফ ক্যাশে বিকল্পটি সরানো হয়েছে (এখন আপডেট লাইব্রেরি বিকল্পটি ব্যবহার করুন)।
- হোয়াটসঅ্যাপে প্রবেশের সময় হুক্সের স্বয়ংক্রিয় আপডেট সরিয়ে ফেলা হয়েছে (এটি কিছু ডিভাইসে সঠিকভাবে কাজ করে না)।
- প্রতিক্রিয়া বিকল্পের জন্য সোয়াইপ সরানো হয়েছে (এটি ডিফল্টরূপে ইতিমধ্যে সক্রিয়)।
- স্টিকারগুলি সক্রিয় করার বিকল্প অপসারণ (এটি ডিফল্টরূপে ইতিমধ্যে সক্রিয়)।
- টেলিফোন কল দ্বারা হোয়াটসঅ্যাপের কল বোতামটি প্রতিস্থাপনের বিকল্প সরানো হয়েছে (একটি পৃথক বোতাম যুক্ত হয়েছিল)।
- সেটিংস বিভাগের কিছু পর্দার ব্যক্তিগতকরণ সরিয়ে ফেলা হয়েছে (আপাতত)।
- অন্যান্য ত্রুটিগুলি স্থির করে।
    </bn>
    <de>
- Alle Datenschutzoptionen wurden erneut hinzugefügt.
- Jetzt können Sie eine Schaltfläche auf dem Unterhaltungsbildschirm hinzufügen, um Anrufe zu tätigen.
- Der Abschnitt mit den Symbolen im Abschnitt "Gespräche" wurde neu strukturiert.
- Neue Methode zum Aktualisieren von Bibliotheken (Hooks). Sie werden jetzt aktualisiert, indem Sie die Option Bibliotheken aktualisieren im Abschnitt Aktualisierungen auswählen.
- Die Option Cache löschen in den Einstellungen wurde entfernt (jetzt die Option Bibliotheken aktualisieren verwenden).
- Das automatische Update von Hooks beim Aufrufen von WhatsApp wurde entfernt (es funktionierte auf einigen Geräten nicht richtig).
- Die Option "Streichen, um zu antworten" wurde entfernt (standardmäßig ist sie bereits aktiviert).
- Option zum Aktivieren von Aufklebern entfernt (standardmäßig bereits aktiviert).
- Option entfernt, um die Anruftaste von WhatsApp durch Telefonanrufe zu ersetzen (eine separate Taste wurde hinzugefügt).
- Die Personalisierung einiger Bildschirme im Bereich "Einstellungen" wurde (vorerst) entfernt.
- Andere Fehler behoben.
	</de>
    <es>
- Se agregaron todas las opciones de privacidad nuevamente.
- Ahora puedes añadir un botón en la pantalla de conversaciones para realizar llamadas de teléfono.
- Restructurada la sección de iconos dentro de la sección Conversaciones.
- Nuevo metodo para actualizar las bibliotecas (Hooks). Ahora se actualizan seleccionando la opción Actualizar bibliotecas, dentro de la sección Actualizaciones.
- Eliminada la sección Borrar cache dentro de Ajustes (Ahora se utiliza la opción Actualizar bibliotecas). 
- Eliminada la actualización automatica de bibliotecas al entrar en WhatsApp (No funcionaba correctamente en algunos dispositivos).
- Eliminada opción deslizar para responder (ya viene activa por defecto).
- Eliminada opción activar Stickers (ya viene activa por defecto).
- Eliminada opción para sustituir el botón de llamadas de WhatsApp por llamadas de teléfono (Se añadió un botón independiente).
- Eliminada personalización de algunas pantallas de la sección Ajustes (por ahora).
- Arreglados otros errores.
    </es>
    <fr>
- Ajout de toutes les options de confidentialité à nouveau.
- Vous pouvez maintenant ajouter un bouton sur l'écran des conversations pour passer des appels téléphoniques.
- Restructuré la section des icônes dans la section Conversations.
- Nouvelle méthode pour mettre à jour les bibliothèques (Hooks). Ils sont maintenant mis à jour en sélectionnant l'option Mettre à jour les bibliothèques, dans la section Mises à jour.
- Suppression de l'option Effacer le cache dans les paramètres (utilisez maintenant l'option Mettre à jour les bibliothèques).
- Suppression de la mise à jour automatique de Hooks lors de la saisie de WhatsApp (cela ne fonctionnait pas correctement sur certains appareils).
- Suppression de l'option "glisser pour répondre" (elle est déjà active par défaut).
- Suppression de l'option d'activation des autocollants (elle est déjà active par défaut).
- Suppression de l'option permettant de remplacer le bouton d'appel de WhatsApp par des appels téléphoniques (un bouton séparé a été ajouté).
- Suppression de la personnalisation de certains écrans de la section Paramètres (pour l'instant).
- Correction d'autres erreurs.
    </fr>
    <hi>
- फिर से सभी गोपनीयता विकल्प जोड़े।
- अब आप फोन कॉल करने के लिए वार्तालाप स्क्रीन पर एक बटन जोड़ सकते हैं।
- वार्तालाप अनुभाग के भीतर आइकन अनुभाग को पुनर्संरचित किया।
- पुस्तकालयों (हुक) को अद्यतन करने की नई विधि। अपडेट अनुभाग में अब वे अद्यतन लाइब्रेरी विकल्प का चयन करके अपडेट किए गए हैं।
- सेटिंग्स में क्लियर कैश विकल्प को हटा दिया (अब अपडेट लाइब्रेरी विकल्प का उपयोग करें)।
- व्हाट्सएप में प्रवेश करते समय हुक के स्वत: अद्यतन को हटा दिया गया (यह कुछ उपकरणों पर सही ढंग से काम नहीं करता था)।
- विकल्प का जवाब देने के लिए स्वाइप हटाया गया (यह पहले से ही डिफ़ॉल्ट रूप से सक्रिय है)।
- स्टिकर को सक्रिय करने के लिए हटाए गए विकल्प (यह पहले से ही डिफ़ॉल्ट रूप से सक्रिय है)।
- टेलीफोन कॉल द्वारा व्हाट्सएप के कॉल बटन को बदलने के लिए हटाए गए विकल्प (एक अलग बटन जोड़ा गया था)।
- सेटिंग्स अनुभाग (अभी के लिए) के कुछ स्क्रीन के निजीकरण को हटा दिया गया।
- अन्य त्रुटियों को ठीक किया।
    </hi>
	<in>
- Menambahkan semua opsi privasi lagi.
- Sekarang Anda dapat menambahkan tombol di layar percakapan untuk melakukan panggilan telepon.
- Merestrukturisasi bagian ikon dalam bagian Percakapan.
- Metode baru untuk memperbarui perpustakaan (Hooks). Mereka sekarang diperbarui dengan memilih opsi Perbarui perpustakaan, di bagian Pembaruan.
- Menghapus opsi Hapus cache di Pengaturan (Sekarang gunakan opsi Perbarui perpustakaan).
- Menghapus pembaruan Hooks otomatis saat memasuki WhatsApp (Tidak berfungsi dengan benar pada beberapa perangkat).
- Gesek dihapus untuk menanggapi opsi (sudah aktif secara default).
- Opsi yang dihapus untuk mengaktifkan Stiker (sudah aktif secara default).
- Opsi yang dihapus untuk mengganti tombol panggilan WhatsApp oleh panggilan telepon (tombol terpisah ditambahkan).
- Personalisasi beberapa layar yang dihapus dari bagian Pengaturan (untuk saat ini).
- Memperbaiki kesalahan lainnya.
	</in>
    <it>
- Aggiunte di nuovo tutte le opzioni sulla privacy.
- Ora puoi aggiungere un pulsante nella schermata delle conversazioni per effettuare chiamate.
- Ristrutturata la sezione icone all'interno della sezione Conversazioni.
- Nuovo metodo per aggiornare le librerie (hook). Ora vengono aggiornati selezionando l'opzione Aggiorna librerie, nella sezione Aggiornamenti.
- Rimossa l'opzione Cancella cache in Impostazioni (ora usa l'opzione Aggiorna librerie).
- Rimosso l'aggiornamento automatico di Hooks durante l'accesso a WhatsApp (non funzionava correttamente su alcuni dispositivi).
- Rimossa l'opzione scorri per rispondere (è già attiva per impostazione predefinita).
- Opzione rimossa per attivare gli adesivi (è già attivo per impostazione predefinita).
- Rimossa l'opzione per sostituire il pulsante di chiamata di WhatsApp con le telefonate (è stato aggiunto un pulsante separato).
- Rimossa la personalizzazione di alcune schermate della sezione Impostazioni (per ora).
- Risolti altri errori.
    </it>
    <nl>
- Alle privacy-opties opnieuw toegevoegd.
- Nu kunt u een knop op het conversatiescherm toevoegen om te bellen.
- Herstructureerde de pictogrammensectie in de sectie Conversaties.
- Nieuwe methode om bibliotheken bij te werken (Hooks). Ze worden nu bijgewerkt door de optie Bibliotheken bijwerken te selecteren in het gedeelte Updates.
- De optie Cache wissen verwijderd in Instellingen (gebruik nu de optie Update bibliotheken).
- De automatische update van Hooks verwijderd bij het invoeren van WhatsApp (op sommige apparaten werkte het niet correct).
- Verwijderde veeg om te reageren optie (deze is standaard al actief).
- Optie verwijderd om Stickers te activeren (deze is standaard al actief).
- Optie verwijderd om de belknop van WhatsApp te vervangen door telefoongesprekken (een aparte knop is toegevoegd).
- Personalisatie van sommige schermen van de sectie Instellingen (voorlopig) verwijderd.
- Andere fouten opgelost.
    </nl>
	<pl>
- Ponownie dodano wszystkie opcje prywatności.
- Teraz możesz dodać przycisk na ekranie rozmowy, aby wykonywać połączenia telefoniczne.
- Przebudowano sekcję ikon w sekcji Rozmowy.
- Nowa metoda aktualizacji bibliotek (haczyki). Są one teraz aktualizowane, wybierając opcję Aktualizuj biblioteki, w sekcji Aktualizacje.
- Usunięto opcję Wyczyść pamięć podręczną w Ustawieniach (Teraz użyj opcji Aktualizuj biblioteki).
- Usunięto automatyczną aktualizację Haków przy wchodzeniu do WhatsApp (Nie działało to poprawnie na niektórych urządzeniach).
- Usunięto przeciągnięcie, by odpowiedzieć (domyślnie jest już aktywne).
- Usunięto opcję aktywacji naklejek (domyślnie jest już aktywna).
- Usunięto opcję zastępowania przycisku połączenia WhatsApp rozmowami telefonicznymi (dodano osobny przycisk).
- Usunięto personalizację niektórych ekranów sekcji Ustawienia (na razie).
- Naprawiono inne błędy.
    </pl>
    <pt>
- Adicionado todas as opções de privacidade novamente.
- Agora você pode adicionar um botão na tela de conversas para fazer chamadas telefônicas.
- Reestruturei a seção de ícones dentro da seção Conversas.
- Novo método para atualizar bibliotecas (ganchos). Eles agora são atualizados selecionando a opção Atualizar bibliotecas, na seção Atualizações.
- Removida a opção Limpar cache nas configurações (agora use a opção Atualizar bibliotecas).
- Removida a atualização automática dos Ganchos ao entrar no WhatsApp (não funcionava corretamente em alguns dispositivos).
- Removido o furto para responder a opção (já está ativo por padrão).
- Removida a opção de ativar Stickers (já está ativa por padrão).
- Removida a opção de substituir o botão de chamada do WhatsApp por ligações telefônicas (foi adicionado um botão separado).
- Removida a personalização de algumas telas da seção Configurações (por enquanto).
- Corrigido outros erros.
    </pt>
	<ro>
- A adăugat din nou toate opțiunile de confidențialitate.
- Acum puteți adăuga un buton pe ecranul conversațiilor pentru a efectua apeluri telefonice.
- Restructurarea secțiunii de icoane din secțiunea Conversații.
- Nouă metodă de actualizare a bibliotecilor (cârlige). Acum sunt actualizate selectând opțiunea Actualizare biblioteci, în secțiunea Actualizări.
- Ați eliminat opțiunea Ștergeți memoria cache din Setări (utilizați acum opțiunea Actualizare biblioteci).
- A eliminat actualizarea automată a Hooks la intrarea WhatsApp (Nu a funcționat corect pe unele dispozitive).
- S-a eliminat opțiunea pentru a răspunde (este deja activă implicit).
- Opțiunea eliminată pentru a activa autocolante (este deja activă implicit).
- Opțiunea eliminată pentru a înlocui butonul de apel al WhatsApp cu apeluri telefonice (a fost adăugat un buton separat).
- Personalizare eliminată a unor ecrane din secțiunea Setări (deocamdată).
- S-au remediat alte erori.
	</ro>
    <ru>
- Добавлены все параметры конфиденциальности снова.
- Теперь вы можете добавить кнопку на экране разговоров, чтобы сделать телефонные звонки.
- Реструктурирован раздел иконок в разделе разговоров.
- Новый метод обновления библиотек (хуки). Теперь они обновляются, выбрав параметр «Обновить библиотеки» в разделе «Обновления».
- Удален параметр Очистить кеш в настройках (теперь используйте параметр Обновить библиотеки).
- Удалено автоматическое обновление хуков при входе в WhatsApp (на некоторых устройствах это работало некорректно).
- Убрана опция «Проведите пальцем до ответа» (по умолчанию она уже активна).
- Удалена опция для активации стикеров (она уже активна по умолчанию).
- Удалена опция замены кнопки вызова в WhatsApp на телефонные звонки (добавлена отдельная кнопка).
- Удалена персонализация некоторых экранов раздела Настройки (на данный момент).
- Исправлены другие ошибки.
    </ru>
    <tr>
- Tüm gizlilik seçeneklerini tekrar eklendi.
- Artık telefon görüşmeleri yapmak için konuşma ekranında bir düğme ekleyebilirsiniz.
- Konuşmalar bölümündeki simgeler bölümünü yeniden yapılandırdık.
- Kütüphaneleri güncellemek için yeni yöntem (Hooks). Şimdi Güncellemeler bölümündeki Kütüphaneleri güncelle seçeneğini seçerek güncellenirler.
- Ayarlar'daki Önbelleği temizle seçeneği kaldırıldı (Şimdi Kütüphaneleri güncelle seçeneğini kullanın).
- WhatsApp'a girerken Kancaların otomatik güncellemesi kaldırıldı (Bazı cihazlarda düzgün çalışmadı).
- Seçeneği yanıtlamak için kaldırılmış kaydırma (zaten varsayılan olarak etkindir).
- Çıkartmaları etkinleştirmek için Kaldır seçeneği (zaten varsayılan olarak etkindir).
- WhatsApp'ın arama düğmesini telefon aramalarıyla değiştirme seçeneği kaldırıldı (ayrı bir düğme eklendi).
- Ayarlar bölümünün bazı ekranlarının kişiselleştirilmesi kaldırıldı (şimdilik).
- Diğer hatalar düzeltildi.
    </tr>
  </update>
</AppUpdater>
