<AppUpdater>
  <update>
    <latestVersion>2.8.1</latestVersion>
    <url>https://github.com/Krowne/App/raw/master/KMod-FWA-v2.8.1.apk</url>
    <en>
- Added again the option to hide the tabs independently.
- Fixed option to hide all tabs.
- Fixed the option that disabling KMod FWA from its settings prevented getting back into the application.
- Fixed other bugs.
    </en>
    <ar>
- تمت إضافة خيار إخفاء علامات التبويب بشكل مستقل مرة أخرى.
- خيار ثابت لإخفاء جميع علامات التبويب.
- تم إصلاح خيار أن تعطيل KMod FWA من إعداداته حال دون العودة إلى التطبيق.
- إصلاح الخلل الأخرى.
    </ar>
    <bn>
- ট্যাবগুলি স্বতন্ত্রভাবে আড়াল করার বিকল্পটি আবার যুক্ত করা হয়েছে।
- সমস্ত ট্যাব আড়াল করার জন্য স্থির বিকল্প।
- কেএমড এফডাব্লুএর সেটিংস থেকে অক্ষম করে দেওয়া বিকল্পটি অ্যাপ্লিকেশনটিতে ফিরে আসতে বাধা দেয় ed
- অন্যান্য বাগ সংশোধন করা হয়েছে।
    </bn>
    <de>
- Es wurde erneut die Option hinzugefügt, die Registerkarten unabhängig voneinander auszublenden.
- Option zum Ausblenden aller Registerkarten behoben.
- Die Option, dass das Deaktivieren von KMod FWA aus den Einstellungen verhindert wurde, wurde behoben.
- Andere Fehler behoben.
	</de>
    <es>
- Añadida de nueva la opción para ocultar las pestañas de forma independiente.
- Arreglada la opción de ocultar todas las pestañas.
- Arreglada la opción que al desactivar KMod FWA desde sus ajustes impedía volver a meterse dentro de la aplicación.
- Arreglados otros errores.
    </es>
    <fr>
- Ajout à nouveau de l'option de masquer les onglets indépendamment.
- Option fixe pour masquer tous les onglets.
- Correction de l'option qui désactivait KMod FWA de ses paramètres empêchait de revenir dans l'application.
- Correction d'autres bugs.
    </fr>
    <hi>
- टैब को स्वतंत्र रूप से छिपाने का विकल्प फिर से जोड़ा गया।
- सभी टैब को छिपाने के लिए निश्चित विकल्प।
- केएमओडी एफडब्ल्यूए को अपनी सेटिंग्स से अक्षम करने वाले विकल्प को एप्लिकेशन में वापस आने से रोक दिया।
- अन्य कीड़े फिक्स्ड।
    </hi>
	<in>
- Menambahkan lagi opsi untuk menyembunyikan tab secara mandiri.
- Opsi tetap untuk menyembunyikan semua tab.
- Memperbaiki opsi yang menonaktifkan KMod FWA dari pengaturannya mencegah masuk kembali ke aplikasi.
- Memperbaiki bug lain.
	</in>
    <it>
- Aggiunta di nuovo l'opzione per nascondere le schede in modo indipendente.
- Opzione fissa per nascondere tutte le schede.
- Risolta l'opzione che disabilitava KMod FWA dalle sue impostazioni impediva il rientro nell'applicazione.
- Risolti altri bug.
    </it>
    <nl>
- Weer de optie toegevoegd om de tabbladen onafhankelijk te verbergen.
- Vaste optie om alle tabbladen te verbergen.
- Oplossing voor de optie dat het uitschakelen van KMod FWA uit de instellingen ervan verhinderde om weer in de applicatie te komen.
- Andere bugs opgelost.
    </nl>
	<pl>
- Dodano ponownie opcję niezależnego ukrywania kart.
- Naprawiono opcję ukrywania wszystkich kart.
- Naprawiono opcję, że wyłączenie KMod FWA z jego ustawień uniemożliwiało powrót do aplikacji.
- Naprawiono inne błędy.
    </pl>
    <pt>
- Adicionada novamente a opção de ocultar as guias independentemente.
- Opção fixa para ocultar todas as guias.
- Corrigida a opção de desativar o KMod FWA de suas configurações, impedindo o retorno ao aplicativo.
- Corrigido outros erros.
    </pt>
	<ro>
- A fost adăugată din nou opțiunea de a ascunde filele în mod independent.
- Opțiune fixă pentru a ascunde toate filele.
- S-a rezolvat opțiunea de dezactivare a KMod FWA de la setările sale, a împiedicat revenirea în aplicație.
- S-au rezolvat alte bug-uri.
	</ro>
    <ru>
- Добавлена снова возможность скрывать вкладки самостоятельно.
- Исправлена опция, позволяющая скрыть все вкладки.
- Исправлена опция, при которой отключение KMod FWA из его настроек препятствовало возврату в приложение.
- Исправлены другие ошибки.
    </ru>
    <tr>
- Sekmeleri bağımsız olarak gizleme seçeneği tekrar eklendi.
- Tüm sekmeleri gizlemek için sabit seçenek.
- KMod FWA'nın ayarlarından devre dışı bırakılmasının uygulamaya geri dönmesini engellediği seçeneği düzeltildi.
- Diğer hatalar düzeltildi.
    </tr>
  </update>
</AppUpdater>
