<AppUpdater>
  <update>
    <latestVersion>2.7.2</latestVersion>
    <url>https://dl-xda.xposed.info/modules/kmod.xposed_v2720_c768a7.apk</url>
    <en>
- Added section to color background the cells of status, in the list of status.
- Optimization of the code, so that it loads the updates faster.
- The option always online was eliminated, for the moment it's not possible for it to work.
- Fixed the option to avoid the deletion of messages.
- The privacy option was corrected, hide audio recording and writing.
- Fixed icons of the call list.
- Other errors were corrected.
    </en>
    <ar>
- إضافة قسم لتلوين خلفية خلايا الحالة ، في قائمة الحالة.
- تحسين الكود ، بحيث يقوم بتحميل التحديثات بشكل أسرع.
- تم إلغاء الخيار دائمًا عبر الإنترنت ، لأنه لا يمكن تشغيله في الوقت الحالي.
- تم إصلاح الخيار لتجنب حذف الرسائل.
- تم تصحيح خيار الخصوصية وإخفاء التسجيل الصوتي والكتابة.
- أيقونات ثابتة من قائمة المكالمات.
- تم تصحيح الأخطاء الأخرى.
    </ar>
    <bn>
- স্ট্যাটাস তালিকায়, অবস্থানের কোষের রঙ পটভূমিতে বিভাগটি যুক্ত করা হয়েছে।
- কোডের অপ্টিমাইজেশান, যাতে এটি দ্রুত আপডেট করে।
- বিকল্পটি সবসময় অনলাইন হ'ল, মুহূর্তের জন্য এটি কাজ করা সম্ভব নয়।
- বার্তাগুলি মুছে ফেলার জন্য বিকল্পটি স্থির করা হয়েছে
- গোপনীয়তা বিকল্প সংশোধন করা হয়েছে, অডিও রেকর্ডিং এবং লেখা লুকান।
- কল তালিকা ফিক্সড আইকন
- অন্যান্য ত্রুটি সংশোধন করা হয়েছে।
    </bn>
    <de>
- Abschnitt zum farbigen Hintergrund der Statuszellen in der Statusliste hinzugefügt.
- Code Optimierungen, Aktualisierungen laden nun schneller.
- Die Option immer Online ist entfernt worden, derzeit funktioniert sie nicht.
- Option zum Vermeiden des Nachrichten löschen behoben.
- Datenschutz Optionen, verstecke aufnehmend und schreibend behoben.
- Symbole der Anrufliste behoben.
- Andere Fehlerbehebungen.
	</de>
    <es>
- Añadida una sección para colorear el fondo de las celdas del estado, en la lista de estado.
- Optimización del código, de forma que carga más rapidas las actualizaciones.
- Eliminada opción siempre en línea, por el momento no es posible.
- Arreglada la opción para evitar la eliminación de mensajes.
- Arreglada la opción de privacidad, ocultar la grabación de audio y escritura.
- Arreglados iconos de la lista de llamadas.
- Arreglados otros errores.
    </es>
    <fr>
- Ajout d'une section pour colorer l'arrière-plan des cellules de statut, dans la liste de statut.
- Optimisation du code, de sorte qu'il charge les mises à jour plus rapidement.
- L’option toujours en ligne a été supprimée, pour le moment il est impossible de fonctionner.
- Correction de l’option pour éviter la suppression des messages.
- L’option de confidentialité a été corrigée, masquer l’enregistrement et l’écriture audio.
- Icônes fixes de la liste d'appels.
- Les autres erreurs ont été corrigées.
    </fr>
    <hi>
- स्थिति की सूची में स्थिति पृष्ठभूमि की पृष्ठभूमि पृष्ठभूमि रंग जोड़ा गया।
- कोड का अनुकूलन, ताकि यह अद्यतनों को तेज़ी से लोड कर सके।
- हमेशा ऑनलाइन विकल्प समाप्त हो गया था, इस पल के लिए यह काम करने के लिए संभव नहीं है।
- संदेशों को हटाने से बचने के लिए विकल्प को फिक्स्ड करें।
- गोपनीयता विकल्प को सही किया गया था, ऑडियो रिकॉर्डिंग और लेखन छुपाएं।
- कॉल सूची के फिक्स्ड आइकॉन।
- अन्य त्रुटियों को सही किया गया था।
    </hi>
	<in>
- Menambahkan bagian ke latar belakang warna sel status, dalam daftar status.
- Optimalisasi kode, sehingga memuat pembaruan lebih cepat.
- Opsi selalu daring dihapuskan, untuk saat ini tidak memungkinkan untuk bekerja.
- Memperbaiki opsi untuk menghindari penghapusan pesan.
- Opsi privasi dikoreksi, sembunyikan rekaman audio dan tulisan.
- Memperbaiki ikon daftar panggilan.
- Kesalahan-kesalahan lainnya telah diperbaiki.
	</in>
    <it>
- Aggiunta sezione per colorare lo sfondo delle celle di stato, nella lista degli stati.
- Ottimizzazione del codice, in modo che carichi gli aggiornamenti più velocemente.
- L'opzione sempre online è stata eliminata, per il momento non è possibile farla funzionare.
- Risolta l'opzione per evitare la cancellazione dei messaggi.
- L'opzione privacy, nascondi la registrazione e la scrittura dell'audio, è stata corretta. 
- Risolto il problema con le icone della lista delle chiamate.
- Correzione di altri errori.
    </it>
    <nl>
- Toegevoegd sectie om de cellen van de status in de achtergrond te kleuren in de lijst met status.
- Optimalisatie van de code, zodat deze de updates sneller laadt.
- De optie altijd online was geëlimineerd, voorlopig is het niet mogelijk om te werken.
- De optie verholpen om te voorkomen dat berichten worden verwijderd.
- De privacyoptie is gecorrigeerd, verberg audio-opname en schrijven.
- Vaste pictogrammen van de oproeplijst.
- Andere fouten zijn gecorrigeerd.
    </nl>	
    <pt>
- Adicionado seção para colorir fundo as células de status, na lista de status.
- Otimização do código, para que carregue as atualizações mais rapidamente.
- A opção sempre online foi eliminada, por enquanto não é possível que funcione.
- Corrigida a opção de evitar a exclusão de mensagens.
- A opção de privacidade foi corrigida, ocultando a gravação e gravação de áudio.
- Ícones fixos da lista de chamadas.
- Outros erros foram corrigidos.
    </pt>
	<ro>
- A fost adăugată secțiunea de fundal de culoare a celulelor de stare, în lista de stare.
- Optimizarea codului, astfel încât să încarce actualizările mai rapid.
- Opțiunea mereu online a fost eliminată, pentru moment nu este posibil ca aceasta să funcționeze.
- S-a reparat opțiunea pentru a evita ștergerea mesajelor.
- Opțiunea de confidențialitate a fost corectată, ascunderea înregistrării audio și ascunderea scrierii .
- Icoanele pentru lista de apeluri au fost reparate.
- Alte erori au fost corectate.
	</ro>
    <ru>
- Добавлен раздел для цветного фона, ячейки статуса, в списке статуса.
- Оптимизация кода, чтобы быстрее загружать обновления.
- Опция всегда онлайн была отключена, на данный момент нет невозможности для ее работы.
- Исправлена опция отменять удаленые сообщения.
- Был изменен параметр конфиденциальности, скрыть набор и запись звука.
- Исправлены значки списка вызовов.
- Исправлены другие ошибки.
    </ru>
    <tr>
- Durum listesinde, durum hücrelerinin arka planını renklendirmek için bölüm eklendi.
- Kodun optimizasyonu, güncellemeleri daha hızlı yükler.
- Her zaman çevrimiçi seçeneği kaldırıldı, şu anda çalışması mümkün değil.
- Mesajların silinmesini önleme seçeneği düzeltildi.
- Gizlilik seçeneği düzeltildi, ses kaydını ve yazmayı gizleyin.
- Arama listesinin simgeleri düzeltildi.
- Diğer hatalar düzeltildi.
    </tr>
  </update>
</AppUpdater>
