<AppUpdater>
  <update>
    <latestVersion>2.3.8</latestVersion>
    <url>http://dl-xda.xposed.info/modules/kmod.xposed_v2_07260e.apk</url>
    <en>
- Added icons of new interface (more information forum XDA-Developers).
- Added customizing floating buttons.
- Added personalization floating button, of message counter, in conversation screen.
- Fix to the latest beta version of Google Play.
- Fixed other bugs.
    </en>
    <bn>
- নতুন ইন্টারফেস আইকন যোগ করা হয়েছে (আরো তথ্য ফোরাম XDA-Deverlopers).
- যোগ করা হয়েছে কাস্টমাইজ ভাসমান বোতাম.
- যোগ করা হয়েছে স্বনির্ধারণ ভাসমান বোতাম, বার্তা কাউন্টার, কথোপকথন পর্দায়.
- গুগল প্লে এর সর্বশেষ বিটা সংস্করণ জন্য সংশোধন.
- অন্যান্য ত্রুটি সংশোধন করা হয়েছে.
    </bn>
    <de>
- Added neue Schnittstelle Icons (mehr Informationen Forum XDA-Developers).
- Added Customizing floating Tasten.
- Added Anpassung Floating-Taste, Nachrichtenzähler , im Gespräch Bildschirm.
- Fixes für die neueste Beta-Version von Google Play.
- Feste andere Fehler.
    </de>
    <es>
- Añadidos iconos de la nueva interfaz (más información en el foro de XDA-Developers).
- Añadida personalización de botones flotantes.
- Añadida personalización del botón flotante, del contador de mensajes, en pantalla de conversación.
- Correcciones para la última versión beta de Google Play.
- Solucionados otros errores.
    </es>
    <hi>
- नया इंटरफ़ेस माउस को जोड़ा गया (और जानकारी के मंच XDA डेवलपर्स)।
- गयी अनुरूपण चल बटन।
- जब जोड़ा गया अनुकूलन चल बटन, संदेश काउंटर, बातचीत स्क्रीन में।
- गूगल प्ले के नवीनतम बीटा संस्करण के लिए फिक्स।
- अन्य त्रुटियों फिक्स्ड।
    </hi>
    <pt>
- Novos ícones da interface Adicionado (mais informações fórum XDA-Developers).
- Personalização Adicionado botões flutuantes.
- Personalização Adicionado botão, contador de mensagens, na tela conversa flutuante.
- Correções para a mais recente versão beta do Google Play.
- Corrigido outros erros.
    </pt>
    <ru>
- Добавлены новые иконки интерфейса (подробнее форум XDA-Developers).
- Добавлены кастомизации плавающие кнопки.
- Добавлена настройка кнопка, счетчик сообщений, в экране разговора с плавающей.
- Исправлены ошибки в последней бета-версии Google Play.
- Исправлены другие ошибки.
    </ru>
    <tr>
- Yeni eklenen arayüz simgeleri (Daha fazla bilgi için forum XDA-Developers).
- Added özelleştirme yüzen düğmeleri.
- Konuşma ekranında butonuna mesaj sayacı, yüzen eklendi özelleştirme.
- Google Play'in son beta sürümü giderir.
- Diğer hatalar düzeltildi.
    </tr>
  </update>
</AppUpdater>
