<AppUpdater>
  <update>
    <latestVersion>2.8.0</latestVersion>
    <url>https://dl-xda.xposed.info/modules/kmod.xposed_v2800_493f1e.apk</url>
    <en>
- Added animated stickers.
- Restructured the interface icons section.
- Fixed interface and conversation icon settings (For a correct display, it's seen only when Android night mode is active).
- The custom ticks have been adapted again, but at the moment the color of the ticks received and read in conversation is not configurable.
- Fixed a bug in which audio notes with avatar activated forced WhatsApp to close.
- Fixed other bugs.
    </en>
    <ar>
- أضيفت ملصقات متحركة.
- إعادة هيكلة قسم أيقونات الواجهة.
- إعدادات ثابتة للواجهة ورمز المحادثة (للعرض الصحيح ، لا يتم رؤيتها إلا عندما يكون الوضع الليلي في Android نشطًا).
- تم تعديل القراد المخصص مرة أخرى ، ولكن في الوقت الحالي ، لا يمكن تكوين لون القراد الذي تم تلقيه وقراءته في المحادثة.
- تم إصلاح الخلل الذي أدى إلى تنشيط الملاحظات الصوتية مع الصورة الرمزية مما أدى إلى إغلاق WhatsApp.
- إصلاح الخلل الأخرى.
    </ar>
    <bn>
- অ্যানিমেটেড স্টিকার যুক্ত হয়েছে।
- ইন্টারফেস আইকন বিভাগ পুনর্গঠিত।
- স্থির ইন্টারফেস এবং কথোপকথনের আইকন সেটিংস (একটি সঠিক প্রদর্শনের জন্য, এটি কেবল তখনই দেখা যায় যখন অ্যান্ড্রয়েড নাইট মোড সক্রিয় থাকে)।
- কাস্টম টিকগুলি আবার মানিয়ে নেওয়া হয়েছে, তবে এই মুহুর্তে কথোপকথনে প্রাপ্ত টিকগুলির রঙ কনফিগারযোগ্য নয়।
- একটি বাগ ঠিক করা হয়েছে যেখানে অবতার সক্রিয়করণ সহ অডিও নোটগুলি বাধ্যতামূলকভাবে হোয়াটসঅ্যাপ বন্ধ করতে বাধ্য করেছে।
- অন্যান্য বাগ সংশোধন করা হয়েছে।
    </bn>
    <de>
- Animierte Aufkleber hinzugefügt.
- Der Abschnitt mit den Schnittstellensymbolen wurde neu strukturiert.
- Die Einstellungen für Benutzeroberfläche und Konversationssymbol wurden korrigiert (für eine korrekte Anzeige wird sie nur angezeigt, wenn der Android-Nachtmodus aktiv ist).
- Die benutzerdefinierten Ticks wurden erneut angepasst, aber im Moment ist die Farbe der im Gespräch empfangenen und gelesenen Ticks nicht konfigurierbar.
- Es wurde ein Fehler behoben, durch den Audio-Notizen mit aktiviertem Avatar WhatsApp zum Schließen zwangen.
- Andere Fehler behoben.
	</de>
    <es>
- Añadidos stickers animados.
- Restructurada la sección de iconos de interfaz.
- Arreglada la configuración de iconos de interfaz y conversaciones (Para una correcta visualización, se ve solo cuando el modo nocturno de Android está activo).
- Se adaptaron de nuevo los ticks personalizados, pero de momento el color de los ticks recibido y leido en conversación no es configurable.
- Corregido un error en el que las notas de audio con avatar activado, forzaban cierre de WhatsApp.
- Corregidos otros errores.
    </es>
    <fr>
- Ajout d'autocollants animés.
- Restructuration de la section des icônes d'interface.
- Paramètres d'interface et d'icône de conversation fixes (pour un affichage correct, il n'est visible que lorsque le mode nuit Android est actif).
- Les ticks personnalisés ont de nouveau été adaptés, mais pour le moment la couleur des ticks reçus et lus en conversation n'est pas configurable.
- Correction d'un bug dans lequel les notes audio avec avatar activé forçaient la fermeture de WhatsApp.
- Correction d'autres bugs.
    </fr>
    <hi>
जोड़ा एनिमेटेड स्टिकर।
- इंटरफ़ेस आइकन अनुभाग को फिर से संगठित किया।
- फिक्स्ड इंटरफेस और बातचीत आइकन सेटिंग्स (एक सही प्रदर्शन के लिए, यह केवल तभी देखा जाता है जब एंड्रॉइड नाइट मोड सक्रिय होता है)।
- कस्टम टिक्स को फिर से अनुकूलित किया गया है, लेकिन फिलहाल टिक्स का रंग और बातचीत में पढ़ा जाने वाला रंग विन्यास योग्य नहीं है।
- एक बग फिक्स्ड जिसमें अवतार के साथ ऑडियो नोट्स सक्रिय व्हाट्सएप को बंद करने के लिए मजबूर किया।
- अन्य कीड़े फिक्स्ड।
    </hi>
	<in>
- Menambahkan stiker animasi.
- Merestrukturisasi bagian ikon antarmuka.
- Pengaturan antarmuka dan ikon percakapan tetap (Untuk tampilan yang benar, itu hanya terlihat ketika mode malam Android aktif).
- Kutu khusus telah disesuaikan lagi, tetapi saat ini warna kutu yang diterima dan dibaca dalam percakapan tidak dapat dikonfigurasi.
- Memperbaiki bug di mana catatan audio dengan avatar diaktifkan memaksa WhatsApp untuk menutup.
- Memperbaiki bug lain.
	</in>
    <it>
- Aggiunti adesivi animati.
- Ristrutturata la sezione delle icone dell'interfaccia.
- Risolto il problema con le impostazioni dell'interfaccia e dell'icona della conversazione (per una visualizzazione corretta, è visibile solo quando è attiva la modalità notte Android).
- I tick personalizzati sono stati nuovamente adattati, ma al momento il colore dei tick ricevuti e letti in conversazione non è configurabile.
- Risolto un bug in cui le note audio con l'avatar attivato attivavano la chiusura di WhatsApp.
- Risolti altri bug.
    </it>
    <nl>
- Geanimeerde stickers toegevoegd.
- De sectie met interfacepictogrammen opnieuw gestructureerd.
- Vaste instellingen voor interface en gesprekspictogrammen (voor een juiste weergave is deze alleen zichtbaar als de Android-nachtmodus actief is).
- De custom ticks zijn weer aangepast, maar op dit moment is de kleur van de ticks die ontvangen en gelezen worden in gesprek niet configureerbaar.
- Een bug opgelost waarbij audionotities met geactiveerde avatar WhatsApp dwongen te sluiten.
- Andere bugs opgelost.
    </nl>
	<pl>
- Dodano animowane naklejki.
- Przebudowano sekcję ikon interfejsu.
- Naprawiono ustawienia interfejsu i ikony konwersacji (dla prawidłowego wyświetlania, jest widoczny tylko wtedy, gdy aktywny jest tryb nocny Androida).
- Niestandardowe tiki zostały ponownie dostosowane, ale w tej chwili kolor tików otrzymanych i odczytanych w rozmowie nie jest konfigurowalny.
- Naprawiono błąd, w którym notatki dźwiękowe z aktywowanym awatarem zmuszały WhatsApp do zamknięcia.
- Naprawiono inne błędy.
    </pl>
    <pt>
- Adicionado adesivos animados.
- Reestruturou a seção de ícones da interface.
- Configurações fixas da interface e do ícone da conversa (para uma exibição correta, ela é vista apenas quando o modo noturno do Android está ativo).
- Os ticks personalizados foram adaptados novamente, mas no momento a cor dos ticks recebidos e lidos na conversa não é configurável.
- Corrigido um erro no qual as anotações de áudio com o avatar ativado obrigavam o fechamento do WhatsApp.
- Corrigido outros erros.
    </pt>
	<ro>
- Adăugate autocolante animate.
- Restructurarea secțiunii de pictograme a interfeței.
- Setări interfață fixă și pictogramă conversație (Pentru o afișare corectă, aceasta este văzută doar atunci când modul de noapte Android este activ).
- Căpușele personalizate au fost adaptate din nou, dar momentan culoarea căpușelor primite și citite în conversație nu este configurabilă.
- S-a remediat o eroare în care notele audio cu avatar activat forțau WhatsApp să închidă.
- S-au rezolvat alte bug-uri.
	</ro>
    <ru>
- Добавлены анимированные наклейки.
- Реструктурирован раздел значков интерфейса.
- Исправлены настройки интерфейса и иконки разговора (для корректного отображения он виден только при активном ночном режиме Android).
- Пользовательские тики были снова адаптированы, но на данный момент цвет тиков, полученных и прочитанных в разговоре, не настраивается.
- Исправлена ошибка, из-за которой звуковые заметки с активированным аватаром заставляли закрываться WhatsApp.
- Исправлены другие ошибки.
    </ru>
    <tr>
- Animasyonlu çıkartmalar eklendi.
- Arayüz simgeleri bölümü yeniden yapılandırıldı.
- Sabit arayüz ve konuşma simgesi ayarları (Doğru bir ekran için sadece Android gece modu etkinken görülür).
- Özel keneler tekrar uyarlanmıştır, ancak şu anda konuşmada okunan ve okunan kenelerin rengi yapılandırılamaz.
- Avatar etkinleştirilen sesli notların WhatsApp'ı kapatmaya zorladığı bir hata düzeltildi.
- Diğer hatalar düzeltildi.
    </tr>
  </update>
</AppUpdater>
