<AppUpdater>
  <update>
    <latestVersion>2.7.8</latestVersion>
    <url>https://dl-xda.xposed.info/modules/kmod.xposed_v2770_ed6e22.apk</url>
    <en>
- Added option to color the text of the menu tabs.
- Added again the menu to customize the main interface icons (it was disabled).
- Fixed bubble customization.
- Fixed the option to add the color to the application title.
- Corrected and restructured the code to assign colors to some sections of WhatsApp (like the status bar).
- Fixed access to the "About .." section.
- Fixed Toast of custom behavior.
- Fixed the Toast that hides the error in privacy.
- Fixed privacy option to hide contacts.
- Fixed a bug that prevented writing in groups.
- Fixed a bug that prevented displaying custom icons in the main menu.
- Fixed the problem of lag.
- Fixed the option to hide contacts and groups (if it doesn't work, delete and add contacts or groups again).
- Fixed some bugs on the conversation screen.
- Fixed option to hide tabs in versions higher than WhatsApp 2.19.289
- Restructured the show/hide calls in conversation section, this created confusion with the new options.
    </en>
    <ar>
- إضافة خيار لتلوين نص علامات التبويب القائمة.
- أضيفت مرة أخرى القائمة لتخصيص رموز الواجهة الرئيسية (تم تعطيله).
- تخصيص فقاعة ثابتة.
- إصلاح خيار إضافة اللون إلى عنوان التطبيق.
- تصحيح وإعادة هيكلة التعليمات البرمجية لتعيين الألوان لبعض أقسام WhatsApp (مثل شريط الحالة).
- وصول ثابت إلى قسم "حول ..".
- نخب ثابت من السلوك المخصص.
- إصلاح نخب الذي يخفي الخطأ في الخصوصية.
- خيار الخصوصية الثابتة لإخفاء جهات الاتصال.
- إصلاح الخلل الذي حال دون الكتابة في مجموعات.
- إصلاح الخلل الذي حال دون عرض الرموز المخصصة في القائمة الرئيسية.
- إصلاح مشكلة التأخر.
- إصلاح خيار إخفاء جهات الاتصال والمجموعات (إذا لم ينجح ذلك ، فقم بحذف وإضافة جهات اتصال أو مجموعات مرة أخرى).
- إصلاح بعض الخلل على شاشة المحادثة.
- خيار ثابت لإخفاء علامات التبويب في إصدارات أعلى من WhatsApp 2.19.289
- إعادة هيكلة إظهار / إخفاء المكالمات في قسم المحادثة ، وهذا خلق ارتباك مع الخيارات الجديدة.
    </ar>
    <bn>
- মেনু ট্যাবগুলির পাঠ্য রঙ করার জন্য বিকল্প যুক্ত করা হয়েছে।
- মূল ইন্টারফেস আইকনগুলি কাস্টমাইজ করতে আবার মেনু যুক্ত করা হয়েছে (এটি অক্ষম করা হয়েছিল)।
- স্থির বুদবুদ কাস্টমাইজেশন।
- অ্যাপ্লিকেশন শিরোনামে রঙ যুক্ত করার বিকল্পটি স্থির করে।
- হোয়াটসঅ্যাপের কিছু বিভাগে (স্ট্যাটাস বারের মতো) রঙ নির্ধারণের জন্য কোডটি সংশোধন ও পুনর্গঠন করা হয়েছে।
- "সম্পর্কে .." বিভাগে স্থির অ্যাক্সেস।
- কাস্টম আচরণের স্থির টোস্ট।
- গোপনীয়তার মধ্যে ত্রুটিটি আড়াল করে এমন টোস্ট স্থির করে দিয়েছে।
- যোগাযোগগুলি গোপন করার জন্য স্থির গোপনীয়তার বিকল্প।
- একটি বাগ সংশোধন করে যা দলে দলে লেখা রোধ করে।
- মুখ্য মেনুতে কাস্টম আইকনগুলি প্রদর্শন করতে বাধা দেয় এমন একটি বাগ সংশোধন করা হয়েছে।
- ল্যাগ সমস্যা স্থির।
- পরিচিতি এবং গোষ্ঠীগুলি গোপন করার বিকল্পটি স্থির করে (যদি এটি কাজ না করে তবে পুনরায় পরিচিতি বা গোষ্ঠীগুলি মুছুন এবং যুক্ত করুন)।
- কথোপকথনের স্ক্রিনে কিছু বাগ সমাধান করা হয়েছে।
- WhatsApp 2.19.289 এর চেয়ে বেশি সংস্করণে ট্যাবগুলি আড়াল করার জন্য স্থির বিকল্প Fix
- কথোপকথন বিভাগে শো / গোপন কলগুলি পুনর্গঠিত, এটি নতুন বিকল্পগুলির সাথে বিভ্রান্তি তৈরি করেছে।
    </bn>
    <de>
- Option hinzugefügt, um den Text der Menü-Registerkarten einzufärben.
- Das Menü zum Anpassen der Hauptoberflächensymbole wurde erneut hinzugefügt (es war deaktiviert).
- Blasenanpassung behoben.
- Die Option, die Farbe zum Titel der Anwendung hinzuzufügen, wurde behoben.
- Der Code wurde korrigiert und neu strukturiert, um einigen Abschnitten von WhatsApp (wie der Statusleiste) Farben zuzuweisen.
- Der Zugriff auf den Abschnitt "Über ..." wurde korrigiert.
- Problem mit benutzerdefiniertem Verhalten behoben.
- Der Toast, der den Fehler in der Privatsphäre versteckt, wurde behoben.
- Die Datenschutzoption zum Ausblenden von Kontakten wurde korrigiert.
- Ein Fehler, der das Schreiben in Gruppen verhinderte, wurde behoben.
- Es wurde ein Fehler behoben, durch den keine benutzerdefinierten Symbole im Hauptmenü angezeigt wurden.
- Das Problem der Verzögerung wurde behoben.
- Die Option zum Ausblenden von Kontakten und Gruppen wurde korrigiert (wenn dies nicht funktioniert, löschen Sie Kontakte oder Gruppen und fügen Sie sie erneut hinzu).
- Einige Fehler auf dem Konversationsbildschirm wurden behoben.
- Option zum Ausblenden von Tabs in höheren Versionen als WhatsApp 2.19.289 behoben
- Das Anzeigen / Verbergen von Anrufen im Konversationsbereich wurde neu strukturiert, was zu Verwirrung mit den neuen Optionen führte.
	</de>
    <es>
- Se añadió la opción para colorear el texto de las pestañas del menú.
- Se añadieron nuevamente los menús para personalizar los íconos de la interfaz principal (ello estaba desactivado).
- Se corrigió la personalización de burbujas.
- Se corrigió la opción de agregar el color al título de la aplicación.
- Se corrigió y reestructuró el código para asignar colores a algunas secciones de WhatsApp (como la barra de estado).
- Se corrigió el acceso a la sección "Acerca de..".
- Se corrigió el Toast del comportamiento personalizado.
- Se corrigió el Toast que oculta el error en la privacidad.
- Se corrigió la opción de privacidad para ocultar contactos.
- Se corrigió un fallo que impedía escribir en grupos.
- Se corrigió un fallo que impedía mostrar los iconos personalizados en el menú principal.
- Se corrigió el problema del lag.
- Se corrigió la opción ocultar contactos y grupos (si no funciona, elimine y agregue los contactos o grupos nuevamente).
- Se corrigieron algunos bugs en la pantalla de conversación.
- Se corrigió la opción para ocultar pestañas en versiones superiores a WhatsApp 2.19.289
- Restructurada la sección de mostrar/ocultar llamadas en conversación, esto creaba confusión con las nuevas opciónes.
    </es>
    <fr>
- Ajout d'une option pour colorer le texte des onglets du menu.
- Ajout du menu pour personnaliser les icônes de l'interface principale (il était désactivé).
- Correction de la personnalisation des bulles.
- Correction de l'option permettant d'ajouter la couleur au titre de l'application.
- Correction et restructuration du code pour attribuer des couleurs à certaines sections de WhatsApp (comme la barre d'état).
- Correction de l'accès à la section "À propos ..".
- Correction du pain grillé du comportement personnalisé.
- Correction du pain grillé qui cache l'erreur dans la vie privée.
- Option de confidentialité fixe pour masquer les contacts.
- Correction d'un bug qui empêchait l'écriture en groupes.
- Correction d'un bug qui empêchait l'affichage des icônes personnalisées dans le menu principal.
- Correction du problème de décalage.
- Correction de l'option permettant de masquer les contacts et les groupes (si cela ne fonctionne pas, supprimez et ajoutez à nouveau des contacts ou des groupes).
- Correction de quelques bugs sur l'écran de conversation.
- Option fixe pour masquer les onglets dans les versions supérieures à WhatsApp 2.19.289
- Restructuré la section Afficher / masquer les appels en conversation, ce qui a créé une confusion avec les nouvelles options.
    </fr>
    <hi>
- मेनू टैब के पाठ को रंग करने के लिए जोड़ा गया विकल्प।
- मुख्य इंटरफ़ेस आइकन (यह अक्षम किया गया था) को अनुकूलित करने के लिए फिर से मेनू जोड़ा गया।
- निश्चित बुलबुला अनुकूलन।
- एप्लिकेशन शीर्षक में रंग जोड़ने का विकल्प तय किया।
- व्हाट्सएप के कुछ अनुभागों (जैसे स्टेटस बार) को रंग असाइन करने के लिए कोड को सही और पुनर्गठित किया।
- "के बारे में .." अनुभाग के लिए निश्चित पहुँच।
- कस्टम व्यवहार का निश्चित टोस्ट।
- गोपनीयता में त्रुटि छुपाता है कि टोस्ट फिक्स्ड।
- संपर्क छिपाने के लिए निश्चित गोपनीयता विकल्प।
- एक बग फिक्स्ड जो समूहों में लेखन को रोकता है।
- मुख्य मेनू में कस्टम आइकन प्रदर्शित करने से रोकने वाली बग को ठीक किया गया।
- लग की समस्या को ठीक किया।
- संपर्क और समूहों को छिपाने का विकल्प तय करें (यदि यह काम नहीं करता है, तो संपर्कों या समूहों को फिर से हटाएं और जोड़ें)।
- बातचीत स्क्रीन पर कुछ कीड़े फिक्स्ड।
- व्हाट्सएप 2.19.289 की तुलना में अधिक संस्करणों में टैब छिपाने का निश्चित विकल्प
- वार्तालाप अनुभाग में शो / छिपी कॉल को फिर से संगठित किया, इससे नए विकल्पों के साथ भ्रम पैदा हुआ।
    </hi>
	<in>
- Opsi yang ditambahkan untuk mewarnai teks dari tab menu.
- Menambahkan lagi menu untuk menyesuaikan ikon antarmuka utama (itu dinonaktifkan).
- Kustomisasi gelembung diperbaiki.
- Memperbaiki opsi untuk menambahkan warna ke judul aplikasi.
- Mengoreksi dan merestrukturisasi kode untuk menetapkan warna ke beberapa bagian WhatsApp (seperti bilah status).
- Memperbaiki akses ke bagian "Tentang ..".
- Memperbaiki Toast dari perilaku khusus.
- Memperbaiki Toast yang menyembunyikan kesalahan dalam privasi.
- Opsi privasi tetap untuk menyembunyikan kontak.
- Memperbaiki bug yang mencegah penulisan dalam grup.
- Memperbaiki bug yang mencegah menampilkan ikon khusus di menu utama.
- Memperbaiki masalah lag.
- Memperbaiki opsi untuk menyembunyikan kontak dan grup (jika tidak berfungsi, hapus dan tambahkan kontak atau grup lagi).
- Memperbaiki beberapa bug di layar percakapan.
- Opsi tetap untuk menyembunyikan tab dalam versi yang lebih tinggi dari WhatsApp 2.19.289
- Restrukturisasi acara / sembunyikan panggilan di bagian percakapan, ini menciptakan kebingungan dengan opsi baru.
	</in>
    <it>
- Aggiunta l'opzione per colorare il testo delle schede dei menu.
- Aggiunto di nuovo il menu per personalizzare le icone dell'interfaccia principale (era disabilitato).
- Risolto il problema della personalizzazione delle bolle.
- Corretta l'opzione per aggiungere il colore al titolo dell'applicazione.
- Corretto e ristrutturato il codice per assegnare i colori ad alcune sezioni di WhatsApp (come la barra di stato).
- Risolto l'accesso alla sezione "Informazioni su".
- Risolto Toast di comportamento personalizzato.
- Risolto il Toast che nasconde l'errore nella privacy.
- Corretta l'opzione di privacy per nascondere i contatti.
- Risolto un bug che impediva la scrittura in gruppi.
- Risolto un bug che impediva la visualizzazione di icone personalizzate nel menu principale.
- Risolto il problema del ritardo.
- Corretta l'opzione per nascondere contatti e gruppi (se non funziona, eliminare e aggiungere nuovamente contatti o gruppi).
- Risolti alcuni bug nella schermata di conversazione.
- Corretta l'opzione per nascondere le schede nelle versioni successive a WhatsApp 2.19.289
- Ristrutturato lo show / nascondi chiamate nella sezione conversazione, questo ha creato confusione con le nuove opzioni.
    </it>
    <nl>
- Optie toegevoegd om de tekst van de menutabs in te kleuren.
- Het menu opnieuw toegevoegd om de pictogrammen van de hoofdinterface aan te passen (het was uitgeschakeld).
- Fixed bubble customization.
- Vaste de optie om de kleur toe te voegen aan de toepassingstitel.
- De code gecorrigeerd en geherstructureerd om kleuren toe te wijzen aan sommige delen van WhatsApp (zoals de statusbalk).
- Vaste toegang tot het gedeelte 'Over ...'.
- Vaste Toast van aangepast gedrag.
- De Toast opgelost die de fout in privacy verbergt.
- Vaste privacy-optie om contacten te verbergen.
- Een bug gerepareerd die schrijven in groepen verhinderde.
- Een bug gerepareerd die het weergeven van aangepaste pictogrammen in het hoofdmenu verhinderde.
- Probleem met vertraging opgelost.
- Vaste de optie om contacten en groepen te verbergen (als het niet werkt, contacten en groepen opnieuw verwijderen en toevoegen).
- Enkele bugs opgelost op het gespreksscherm.
- Vaste optie om tabbladen te verbergen in versies hoger dan WhatsApp 2.19.289
- Herstructurering van de show / hide-oproepen in de gesprekssectie, dit creëerde verwarring met de nieuwe opties.
    </nl>
	<pl>
- Dodano opcję pokolorowania tekstu kart menu.
- Dodano ponownie menu, aby dostosować ikony głównego interfejsu (zostało wyłączone).
- Naprawiono dostosowywanie baniek.
- Naprawiono opcję dodawania koloru do tytułu aplikacji.
- Poprawiono i zrestrukturyzowano kod, aby przypisać kolory do niektórych sekcji WhatsApp (takich jak pasek stanu).
- Naprawiono dostęp do sekcji „About ..”.
- Naprawiono Toast niestandardowego zachowania.
- Naprawiono Toast, który ukrywa błąd w prywatności.
- Naprawiono opcję prywatności, aby ukryć kontakty.
- Naprawiono błąd, który uniemożliwiał pisanie w grupach.
- Naprawiono błąd, który uniemożliwiał wyświetlanie niestandardowych ikon w menu głównym.
- Naprawiono problem opóźnienia.
- Naprawiono opcję ukrywania kontaktów i grup (jeśli to nie działa, usuń i dodaj kontakty lub grupy ponownie).
- Naprawiono kilka błędów na ekranie rozmowy.
- Naprawiono opcję ukrywania zakładek w wersjach wyższych niż WhatsApp 2.19.289
- Restrukturyzowano pokazywanie / ukrywanie połączeń w sekcji konwersacji, co spowodowało zamieszanie w nowych opcjach.
    </pl>
    <pt>
- Adicionado opção para colorir o texto das guias do menu.
- Adicionado novamente o menu para personalizar os principais ícones da interface (ele foi desativado).
- Customização de bolha fixa.
- Corrigida a opção de adicionar a cor ao título do aplicativo.
- Corrigido e reestruturado o código para atribuir cores a algumas seções do WhatsApp (como a barra de status).
- Acesso fixo à seção "Sobre ..".
- Corrigido brinde de comportamento personalizado.
- Corrigido o Toast que oculta o erro na privacidade.
- Corrigida opção de privacidade para ocultar contatos.
- Corrigido um bug que impedia a gravação em grupos.
- Corrigido um erro que impedia a exibição de ícones personalizados no menu principal.
- Corrigido o problema de atraso.
- Corrigida a opção de ocultar contatos e grupos (se não funcionar, exclua e adicione contatos ou grupos novamente).
- Corrigidos alguns erros na tela de conversação.
- Corrigida opção para ocultar guias em versões superiores ao WhatsApp 2.19.289
- Reestruturou a seção mostrar / ocultar chamadas na seção de conversa, criando confusão com as novas opções.
    </pt>
	<ro>
- Opțiune adăugată pentru a colora textul filelor din meniu.
- A fost adăugat din nou meniul pentru a personaliza pictogramele principale ale interfeței (a fost dezactivat).
- Personalizare fixă cu bule.
- S-a rezolvat opțiunea de a adăuga culoarea la titlul aplicației.
- Corectat și restructurat codul pentru a atribui culori unor secțiuni de WhatsApp (cum ar fi bara de stare).
- Acces fix la secțiunea „Despre ..”.
- Toast fix al comportamentului personalizat.
- A remediat Toastul care ascunde eroarea în confidențialitate.
- Opțiune de confidențialitate fixă pentru a ascunde contactele.
- S-a rezolvat o eroare care a împiedicat scrierea în grupuri.
- S-a remediat o eroare care împiedică afișarea pictogramelor personalizate în meniul principal.
- S-a rezolvat problema întârzierii.
- S-a remediat opțiunea de a ascunde contactele și grupurile (dacă nu funcționează, ștergeți și adăugați din nou contacte sau grupuri).
- S-au rezolvat unele bug-uri pe ecranul de conversație.
- Opțiune fixă pentru a ascunde file în versiuni mai mari decât WhatsApp 2.19.289
- Restructurarea apelurilor / ascunderii apelurilor în secțiunea de conversație, acest lucru a creat confuzie cu noile opțiuni.
	</ro>
    <ru>
- Добавлена опция для раскраски текста вкладок меню.
- Добавлено еще раз меню для настройки основных значков интерфейса (оно было отключено).
- Исправлена настройка пузырей.
- Исправлена опция добавления цвета в заголовок приложения.
- Исправлен и реструктурирован код, чтобы назначать цвета некоторым разделам WhatsApp (например, строке состояния).
- Исправлен доступ к разделу «О ..».
- Исправлен тост нестандартного поведения.
- Исправлен тост, который скрывает ошибку в приватности.
- Исправлена опция конфиденциальности, чтобы скрыть контакты.
- Исправлена ошибка, которая мешала записи в группах.
- Исправлена ошибка, которая мешала отображению пользовательских значков в главном меню.
- Исправлена проблема отставания.
- Исправлена возможность скрывать контакты и группы (если это не работает, удалите и добавьте контакты или группы снова).
- Исправлены некоторые ошибки на экране разговора.
- Исправлена опция, позволяющая скрывать вкладки в версиях выше, чем WhatsApp 2.19.289.
- Изменена структура отображения / скрытия звонков в разделе разговоров, что создало путаницу с новыми параметрами.
    </ru>
    <tr>
- Menü sekmelerinin metnini renklendirme seçeneği eklendi.
- Ana arayüz simgelerini özelleştirmek için tekrar menü eklendi (devre dışı bırakıldı).
- Sabit kabarcık özelleştirme.
- Uygulama başlığına renk ekleme seçeneği düzeltildi.
- WhatsApp'ın bazı bölümlerine (durum çubuğu gibi) renk atamak için kod düzeltildi ve yeniden yapılandırıldı.
- "Hakkında .." bölümüne erişim düzeltildi.
- Özel davranış Tost Sabit.
- Gizliliği hatayı gizleyen Tost düzeltildi.
- Kişileri gizlemek için Sabit gizlilik seçeneği.
- Grup halinde yazmayı engelleyen bir hata düzeltildi.
- Ana menüde özel simgeler görüntülenmesini engelleyen bir hata düzeltildi.
- Gecikme sorunu düzeltildi.
- Kişileri ve grupları gizleme seçeneği düzeltildi (çalışmazsa, kişileri veya grupları yeniden silme ve silme).
- Konuşma ekranında bazı hatalar düzeltildi.
- WhatsApp 2.19.289’dan daha yüksek sürümlerde sekmeleri gizleme seçeneği düzeltildi.
- Konuşma bölümünde show / hide çağrılarını yeniden yapılandırdı, bu yeni seçeneklerle karışıklık yarattı.
    </tr>
  </update>
</AppUpdater>
