<AppUpdater>
  <update>
    <latestVersion>2.5.6</latestVersion>
    <url>http://dl-xda.xposed.info/modules/kmod.xposed_v2_7217e4.apk</url>
    <en>
- Added options to hide writing and recording audio in the privacy section.
- Added option to hide when connected from within WhatsApp.
- Added French language.
- Delete the privacy option to see the last connection of the others and hide the own, until  problem solved.
- Delete KMod shortcut button from WhatsApp Settings, now accessed with the menu button on the main interface.
- Fixed other issues.
    </en>
    <ar>
- إضافة خيارات، لإخفاء الكتابة وسجل الصوت، في قسم الخصوصية.
- إضافة خيار لإخفاء عند الاتصال من داخل ال واتساب.
- إضافة اللغة الفرنسية.
- حذف خيار الخصوصية لمعرفة آخر اتصال للآخرين وإخفاء الخاصة، حتى حل المشكلة.
- حذف زر كمود الاختصار من إعدادات ال واتساب، والوصول إليها الآن مع زر القائمة على الواجهة الرئيسية.
- قضايا أخرى ثابتة.
    </ar>
    <bn>
- গোপনীয়তা বিভাগে লেখার এবং রেকর্ড অডিও লুকানোর জন্য বিকল্পগুলি যোগ করা হয়েছে
- হোয়াটসঅ্যাপের মধ্যে থেকে সংযুক্ত যখন সংযুক্ত করার জন্য বিকল্পটি যুক্ত করা হয়েছে
- ফ্রেঞ্চ ভাষা যোগ করা হয়েছে
- সমস্যাটি সমাধান না হওয়া পর্যন্ত, অন্যদের শেষ সংযোগটি দেখতে এবং গোপন করার গোপনীয়তা বিকল্পটি মুছুন।
- হোয়াটসঅ্যাপ সেটিংস থেকে কেমোড শর্টকাট বোতাম মুছুন, এখন প্রধান ইন্টারফেসের মেনু বোতামের সাথে অ্যাক্সেস করুন।
- স্থির অন্যান্য সমস্যা।
    </bn>
    <de>
- Option zum verstecken von schreibt und nimmt Audio auf, in der Privatsphäre Sektion hinzugefügt. 
- Option zum verstecken wann man verbunden ist innerhalb von WhatsApp hinzugefügt. 
- Französische Sprache hinzugefügt. 
- Privatsphäre Option, um andere letzte Verbindung zu sehen und eigene zu verstecken, gelöscht, bis Problem gelöst ist. 
- KMod Verknüpfungsschaltfläche in den WhatsApp Einstellungen gelöscht, nun von der Menüschaltfläche im Hauptbildschirm aus erreichbar. 
- Andere Probleme gelöst.
	</de>
    <es>
- Añadidas opciones, para ocultar Escribiendo y Grabando audio, en la sección de privacidad.
- Añadida opción para ocultar cuando se está conectado desde dentro de WhatsApp.
- Añadido idioma Frances.
- Borrada la opción de privacidad para ver la última conexión de los demás y ocultar la propia, hasta solucionar el problema.
- Borrado botón de acceso directo a KMod desde Ajustes de WhatsApp, ahora se accede con el botón de menu de la interfaz principal.
- Arreglados otros problemas.
    </es>
    <fr>
- Ajout d'options pour cacher l'écriture et l'enregistrement d'audio dans la section de confidentialité.
- Ajout d'une option pour se cacher lorsqu'elle est connectée dans WhatsApp.
- Ajout de langue française.
- Supprimer l'option de confidentialité pour voir la dernière connexion des autres et cacher les propres, jusqu'à ce que le problème soit résolu.
- Supprimez le bouton raccourci KMod à partir des paramètres de WhatsApp, maintenant accessible avec le bouton de menu sur l'interface principale.
- Correction d'autres problèmes.
    </fr>
    <hi>
- गोपनीयता अनुभाग में, लिखने और रिकॉर्ड ऑडियो को छिपाने के लिए, विकल्प जोड़े गए।
- व्हाट्सएप के अंदर से जुड़े होने पर छिपाने के लिए विकल्प जोड़ा गया।
- फ्रेंच भाषा जोड़ा गया
- समस्या का समाधान करने तक, दूसरे के अंतिम कनेक्शन को देखने और खुद को छुपाने के लिए गोपनीयता विकल्प को हटा दें।
- व्हाट्सएप सेटिंग्स से केमोद शॉर्टकट बटन को हटाएं, जो अब मुख्य इंटरफ़ेस पर मेनू बटन से पहुंचा है।
- फिक्स्ड अन्य मुद्दों।
    </hi>
    <it>
- Aggiunta opzione per nascondere la scritta "sta scrivendo" e "sta registrando audio", nelle opzioni Privacy. 
- Aggiunta opzione per nascondersi quando collegati da WhatsApp. 
- Aggiunta lingua francese. 
- Eliminata l'opzione privacy per vedere l'ultima connessione degli altri contatti nascondendo la propria, fino alla risoluzione del problema. 
- Eliminato il pulsante con il collegamento a KMod dai settaggi di WhatsApp, ora accessibile con il pulsante menù nell'interfaccia principale. 
- Sistemati altri problemi. 
    </it>
    <nl>
- Opties toegevoegd, om schrijf en opnemen van audio in het privé sectie.
- Optie toegevoegd om je te verbergen als je verbonden bent in WhatsApp. 
- Franse taal toegevoegd. 
- Privé optie verwijderd van laatst geziene verbinding en ook dat van andere totdat het probleem is opgelost. 
- KMod snelkoppeling verwijderd uit de WhatsApp instellingen, dat staat nu met menu knop in het hoofd menu. 
- Andere problemen verholpen.
    </nl>	
    <pt>
- Adicionado opções, para ocultar gravação e gravação de áudio, na seção de privacidade.
- Adicionado opção para ocultar quando conectado a partir do WhatsApp.
- Adicionado idioma francês.
- Excluída a opção de privacidade para ver a última conexão dos outros e esconder o próprio, até resolver o problema.
- Excluída KMod atalho botão de WhatsApp Configurações, agora acessado com o botão de menu na interface principal.
- Corrigido outros problemas.
    </pt>
    <ru>
- Добавлены опции, чтобы скрыть написание сообщения и записи аудио, в разделе конфиденциальность.
- Добавлена возможность скрывать подключение внутри WhatsApp.
- Добавлен французский язык.
- Удалены параметры конфиденциальности, видеть последнее подключение других и скрывать собственные, пока не решу проблему.
- Удалена кнопка ярлыка KMod из настроек whatsapp, теперь она доступна в меню на главном экране. 
- Другие мелкие исправления.
    </ru>
    <tr>
- Gizlilik sekmesine ses kaydı ve mesaj gönderme bilgilendirmelerini gizleme ayarı eklendi.
- Çevrimiçi bilgilendirmesini gizleme eklendi.
- Fransızca eklendi.
- Son görülme'yi gizleme ayarı problemler çözülünceye kadar silindi.
- WhatsApp ayarlarından KMod kısayolu silindi, artık ana ekran menüsünden erişim sağlayabillirsiniz.
- Bazı hatalar giderildi.
    </tr>
  </update>
</AppUpdater>
