<AppUpdater>
  <update>
    <latestVersion>2.6.7</latestVersion>
    <url>https://dl-xda.xposed.info/modules/kmod.xposed_v2670_f62781.apk</url>
    <en>
- Android SDK update to version 27.
- Added option to avoid the deletion of messages sent by your contacts.
- Added option to show the connection or disconnection of your contacts (It only works with the contacts in which you have entered a conversation when entering WhatsApp).
- Now when an option is broken, it will not break the other KMod FWA options.
- Now when you update KMod FWA, the Hooks will be updated automatically when you enter WhatsApp.
- Update to the latest Betas.
- Added Indonesian language.
- Correction of the option to delete messages of any date.
- Fixed other problems.
    </en>
    <ar>
- تحديث أندرويد سك إلى الإصدار 27.
- إضافة خيار لتجنب حذف الرسائل المرسلة من قبل جهات الاتصال لدينا.
- إضافة خيار لإظهار الاتصال أو قطع الاتصال لدينا (يعمل فقط مع جهات الاتصال التي دخلنا محادثتك عند دخول ال واتساب).
- الآن عندما يتم كسر خيار، فإنه لن كسر خيارات كمود فوا الأخرى.
- الآن عند تحديث كمود فوا، سيتم تحديث السنانير تلقائيا عند إدخال ال واتساب.
- تحديث لأحدث بيتاس.
- واضاف اللغة الاندونيسية.
- تصحيح الخيار لحذف رسائل من أي تاريخ.
- مشاكل أخرى ثابتة.
    </ar>
    <bn>
- সংস্করণ 27 এ অ্যানড্রইড এসডিকি আপডেট
- আমাদের পরিচিতি দ্বারা প্রেরিত বার্তাগুলি মুছে ফেলতে এড়াতে বিকল্পটি যুক্ত করা হয়েছে।
- আমাদের পরিচিতিগুলির সংযোগ বা সংযোগ বিচ্ছিন্ন করার জন্য বিকল্পটি যুক্ত করা হয়েছে (এটি শুধুমাত্র এমন পরিচিতিগুলির সাথে কাজ করে যা আমরা আপনার কথোপকথনে প্রবেশ করে যখন হোয়াটফিট প্রবেশ করিয়েছি)।
- এখন যখন একটি বিকল্প ভাঙ্গা হয়, এটি অন্য কেওমোড FWA বিকল্পগুলি ভাঙ্গবে না।
- এখন যখন আপনি কেমোড এফডব্লুএ আপডেট করবেন তখন হুক্স স্বয়ংক্রিয়ভাবে আপডেট হবে যখন আপনি হোয়াটসঅ্যাপ প্রবেশ করবেন।
- সর্বশেষ বিটাস আপডেট করুন
- ইন্দোনেশিয়ার ভাষা যোগ করা
- কোনো তারিখ বার্তা মুছে ফেলার বিকল্প সংশোধন
- স্থায়ী অন্যান্য সমস্যা।
    </bn>
    <de>
- Android SDK Aktualisierung zu Version 27.
- Option zum Vermeiden der Löschung von Nachrichten, die von deinen Kontakten gesendet wurden, hinzugefügt.
- Option zum Anzeigen der Verbindung und Trennung deiner Kontakte hinzugefügt (Es funktioniert nur mit Kontakten mit denen du eine Unterhaltung begonnen hast, wenn WhatsApp geöffnet wird).
- Wenn nun eine Option defekt ist, wird sie nicht andere KMod FWA Optionen stören.
- Wenn du nun KMod FWA aktualisierst werden die Haken automatisch aktualisiert sobald du WhatsApp öffnest.
- Zu letzten Betas aktualisierst
- Indonesisch Sprache hinzugefügt. 
- Korrektur der Option zum löschen von Nachrichten jeglichen Datums.
- Andere Probleme behoben.
	</de>
    <es>
- Actualización de Android SDK a la versión 27.
- Añadida opción para evitar la eliminación de mensajes enviados por nuestros contactos.
- Añadida opción para mostrar la conexión o desconexión de nuestros contactos (Solo funciona con los contactos en los que hemos entrado en su conversación al entrar en WhatsApp).
- Ahora cuando se rompa una opción, no romperá al resto de opciónes de KMod FWA.
- Ahora cuando actualices KMod FWA, los Hooks se actualizarán automaticamente al entrar en WhatsApp.
- Actualización a las últimas Betas.
- Añadido idioma Indonesio.
- Corrección de la opción para eliminar mensajes de cualquier fecha.
- Arreglados otros problemas.
    </es>
    <fr>
- Mise à jour Android SDK à la version 27.
- Ajout d'une option pour éviter la suppression des messages envoyés par nos contacts.
- Ajout d'une option pour montrer la connexion ou la déconnexion de nos contacts (Cela ne fonctionne qu'avec les contacts dans lesquels nous avons entré votre conversation en entrant dans WhatsApp).
- Maintenant, quand une option est cassée, elle ne va pas casser les autres options de KMod FWA.
- Maintenant, lorsque vous mettez à jour KMod FWA, les Hooks seront mis à jour automatiquement lorsque vous entrez dans WhatsApp.
- Mise à jour vers les derniers Betas.
- Ajout de langue indonésien.
- Correction de l'option de suppression des messages de n'importe quelle date.
- Correction d'autres problèmes.
    </fr>
    <hi>
- संस्करण 27 में एंड्रॉइड एसडीके अपडेट
- हमारे संपर्कों द्वारा भेजे गए संदेशों के विलोपन से बचने के लिए विकल्प जोड़ा गया
- हमारे संपर्कों का कनेक्शन या वियोग का पता लगाने के लिए जोड़ा गया विकल्प (यह केवल उन संपर्कों के साथ काम करता है जिसमें हम WhatsApp में प्रवेश करते समय अपनी बातचीत दर्ज कर चुके हैं)
- अब जब कोई विकल्प टूट जाता है, तो वह अन्य केडॉड एफडब्ल्यूए विकल्पों को तोड़ नहीं सकता है।
- अब जब आप केमोड एफडब्ल्यूए को अपडेट करते हैं, तो जब आप व्हाट्सएप में प्रवेश करते हैं तो हुक स्वचालित रूप से अपडेट हो जाएगा।
- नवीनतम बीटास में अपडेट करें
- जोड़ा गया इंडोनेशियाई भाषा
- किसी भी तिथि के संदेशों को हटाने के विकल्प का सुधार।
- फिक्स्ड अन्य समस्याएं
    </hi>
	<in>
- Android SDK diperbarui ke versi 27.
- Tambahan opsi untuk mencegah penghapusan pesan yang dikirim oleh kontak anda.
- Tambahan opsi untuk menampilkan sambungan koneksi atau pemutusan koneksi kontak anda (hanya bekerja pada kontak yang telah memiliki percakapan saat masuk WhatsApp).
- Jika sebuah opsi gagal, tidak akan mengganggu opsi KMod FWA yang lain.
- Ketika memperbarui KMod FWA, Hooks akan diperbarui secara otomatis ketika memasuki WhatsApp.
- Diperbarui ke versi Beta terbaru.
- Ditambahkan bahasa indonesia.
- Koreksi dari opsi untuk menghapus pesan di tanggal apa saja.
- Perbaikan beberapa masalah lainnya.
	</in>
    <it>
- Android SDK aggiornato alla versione 27.
- Aggiunta opzione per evitare la cancellazione di messaggi spediti dai propri contatti.
- Aggiunta opzione per mostrare la connessione o la disconnessione dei propri contatti (funziona solamente con i contatti con i quali è stata iniziata una conversazione durante l'ingresso in WhatsApp).
- Adesso, quando un'opzione si interrompe, non interromperà le altre opzioni di KMod FWA.
- Adesso, all'aggiornamento di KMod FWA, gli agganci verranno aggiornati automaticamente all'ingresso in WhatsApp.
- Aggiornato alle ultime Beta.
- Aggiunta lingua indonesiano.
- Correzione dell'opzione per cancellare i messaggi di qualsiasi data.
- Sistemati altri problemi.
    </it>
    <nl>
- Android SDK-update naar versie 27.
- Optie toegevoegd om te voorkomen dat berichten worden verwijderd door onze contactpersonen.
- Optie toegevoegd om de verbinding of verbreking van onze contacten te tonen (het werkt alleen met de contacten waarin wij uw gesprek hebben ingevoerd bij het invoeren van WhatsApp).
- Wanneer een optie wordt verbroken, zal dit de andere KMod FWA-opties niet breken.
- Als u KMod FWA nu update, worden de hooks automatisch bijgewerkt wanneer u WhatsApp invoert.
- Update naar de nieuwste bèta's.
- Indonesisch taal toegevoegd. 
- Correctie van de optie om berichten van welke datum dan ook te verwijderen.
- Andere problemen verholpen.
    </nl>	
    <pt>
- Atualizada para a SDK 27 do Android.
- Adicionada opção para evitar a deleção de mensagens de contatos.
- Adicionada a opção de mostrar a conexão ou desconexão de contatos (apenas funciona se o contato entrou na conversa quando abriu o Whatsapp)
- Agora quando uma opção se quebra, não ira quebrar as outras opções do KMod que ainda funciona.
- Agora quando o KMod FWF for atualizado, os hooks serão limpos e reaplicados quando abrir o Whatsapp.
- Update para a ultima beta.
- Adicionado idioma indonésio.
- Correção na opção de apagar mensagens de qualquer data.
- Outras correções de bugs.
    </pt>
    <ru>
- Обновление Android SDK до версии 26.
- Добавлена ​​возможность избегать удаления сообщений, отправленных Вашими контактами.
- Добавлена ​​опция показать соединение или отключение наших контактов (она работает только с контактами, с которые Вы вошли в разговор в WhatsApp).
- Теперь, когда опция сломана, она не нарушит другие параметры KMod FWA.
- Теперь, когда Вы обновляете KMod FWA, галки будут автоматически обновляться при входе в WhatsApp.
- Работает с последними бета-версиями.
- Добавлен индонезийский язык.
- Исправлена ​​возможность удаления сообщений любой даты.
- Исправлены другие проблемы.
    </ru>
    <tr>
- Android SDK 27.sürüm güncelleştirmesi.
- Kişileriniz tarafından gönderilen mesajların silinmesini engelleme seçeneği eklendi.
- Kişilerinizin giriş ve çıkışlarını gösterme seçeneği eklendi (Bu özellik sadece Whatsapp'a giriş yaparken sizin konuşmalarınıza giren kişiler için geçerlidir).
- Artık bir seçenek bozulduğunda, diğer KMod FWA seçeneklerini bozmayacak.
- KMod FWA'yı güncelleştirip, Whatsapp'a giriş yaptığınızda kancalar otomatik olarak güncelleştirilecek.
- Son Betalar için güncelleştirme.
- Endonezya eklendi.
- Tarih sınırlaması olmadan mesaj silme seçeneği düzeltildi.
- Diğer problemler düzeltildi.
    </tr>
  </update>
</AppUpdater>
