<AppUpdater>
  <update>
    <latestVersion>2.4.5</latestVersion>
    <url>http://dl-xda.xposed.info/modules/kmod.xposed_v2_16fc64.apk</url>
    <en>
- Added a new bubble.
- Added highlight in groups.
- Added highlight in contacts (up to 3).
- Added support for GIF Gallery.
- Added option to hide last connection (you'll see the last connection of the other, but they not yours).
- Added Italian language
- Fixed backup section, you can now save and load properly themes with background images.
- Fixes for the latest beta version of Google Play.
- Fixed other errors.
    </en>
    <bn>
- একটি নতুন বুদ্বুদ যোগ করা হয়েছে.
- দলের মধ্যে হাইলাইট যোগ করা হয়েছে.
- পরিচিতি (3 পর্যন্ত) মধ্যে হাইলাইট যোগ করা হয়েছে.
- জিআইএফ গ্যালারি জন্য সমর্থন যোগ করা হয়েছে.
- যোগ করা হয়েছে গত সংযোগ লুকাতে বিকল্প (তুমি একে অপরের গত সংযোগ দেখতে পাবেন, কিন্তু তারা না পুলিশের).
- যোগ করা হয়েছে ইতালীয় ভাষা
- করতে ব্যাকআপ অধ্যায় ফিক্সড, আপনি এখন সংরক্ষণ এবং সঠিকভাবে ব্যাকগ্রাউন্ড ইমেজ সঙ্গে থিম লোড.
- গুগল প্লে এর সর্বশেষ বিটা সংস্করণ জন্য সংশোধন.
- অন্যান্য ত্রুটি সংশোধন করা হয়েছে.
    </bn>
    <de>
- Eine neue Blase hinzugefügt. 
- Hinzugefügt Highlight in Gruppen. 
- Hinzugefügt Highlight in Kontakten (bis zu 3).
- Zusätzliche Unterstützung für GIF-Galerie. 
- Option hinzugefügt, um letzte Verbindung verstecken (Sie werden die letzte Verbindung des anderen sehen, aber sie nicht verkaufen). 
- Hinzugefügt italienische Sprache
- Backup-Abschnitt wurde behoben,  Sie können jetzt Themen mit Hintergrundbildern laden. 
- Fehlerbehebungen für die neueste Beta-Versionen aus dem Google Play. 
- Fehlerbehebungen von anderen Fehlern
    </de>
    <es>
- Añadida una nueva burbuja.
- Añadido resalte en grupos.
- Añadido resalte en contactos (hasta 3).
- Añadido soporte para GIF en Galería.
- Añadido opción para ocultar última conexión (tu verás la de los demás).
- Añadido idioma Italiano.
- Arreglada sección copia de seguridad, ahora puedes guardar y cargar temas correctamente con sus imagenes de fondo.
- Correcciones para la última versión beta de Google Play.
- Solucionados otros errores.
    </es>
    <hi>
- एक नया बुलबुला जोड़ा।
- समूहों में प्रकाश डाला गया है।
- संपर्क (3 तक) में प्रकाश डाला गया है।
- GIF गैलरी के लिए समर्थन जोड़ा गया।
- गयी अंतिम कनेक्शन छिपाने के लिए विकल्प (आप दूसरे के अंतिम कनेक्शन देखेंगे, लेकिन वे नहीं तुम्हारा)।
- गयी इतालवी भाषा
- बैकअप कर सकते हैं अनुभाग तय, अब आप को बचाने के लिए और ठीक पृष्ठभूमि छवियों के साथ विषयों लोड।
- गूगल प्ले के नवीनतम बीटा संस्करण के लिए फिक्स।
- अन्य त्रुटियों फिक्स्ड।
    </hi>
    <pt>
- Adicionado uma nova "bolha".
- Destaque adicionado para grupos.
- Destaque adicionado para contatos (até 3).
- Adicionado suporte para Galeria GIF.
- Opção para ocultar última conexão adicionada (você verá a última conexão do outro, mas não verá a sua).
- Adicionada língua italiana
- Corrigido seção de backup, agora você poderá salvar e carregar corretamente os temas com imagens de fundo.
- Correções para a mais recente versão beta do Google Play.
- Corrigido outros erros.
    </pt>
    <ru>
- Добавлен новый пузырь.
- Добавлена подсветка в группах.
- Добавлена подсветка в контактах (до 3).
- Добавлена поддержка GIF в Галерее.
- Добавлена опция для скрытия последнего соединения (вы увидите последнее подключение других, а они твои нет).
- Добавлен итальянский язык.
- Исправлена ошибка резервного копирования раздела, теперь вы можете правильно сохранять и загружать темы с фоновыми изображениями.
- Исправления для последней бета-версии Google Play.
- Исправлены другие ошибки.
    </ru>
    <tr>
-Yeni bir balon eklendi
-Grup konuşmalarını vurgulayabilirsiniz.
-Konuşmaları vurgulayabilirsiniz (3 kişiye kadar).
-GIF galerisi desteği eklendi.
-Son görülmeyi gizleme eklendi (diğerlerinin son görülmesini görebilirsiniz ancak onlar sizinkini göremez)
-İtalyanca eklendi
-Yedekleme işlevi düzeltildi, artık temaları düzgünce yükleyebilir ya da yedekleyebilirsiniz.
-Google Play'de ki son beta için hatalar düzeltildi.
-Diğer hatalar düzeltildi
    </tr>
  </update>
</AppUpdater>
