<AppUpdater>
  <update>
    <latestVersion>2.5.9</latestVersion>
    <url>http://dl-xda.xposed.info/modules/kmod.xposed_v2_8abe7f.apk</url>
    <en>
- Added option to set photos in the state with the highest quality.
- Added option to increase the time of the videos of the state, up to 5 minutes (only visible in devices with this option active).
- Now the statusbar becomes the same color as the header (Android 5.0+).
- Deleted option to color the TAB in the conversations (until problem can be solved).
- Fixed problem of the highlight contacts option.
- Fixed problem of the option to deactivate the delivery report.
- Fixed other errors.
    </en>
    <ar>
- إضافة خيار لإرسال الصور في الدولة مع أعلى مستويات الجودة.
- إضافة خيار لزيادة الوقت من أشرطة الفيديو للدولة، وتصل إلى 5 دقائق (مرئية فقط في الأجهزة مع هذا الخيار نشط).
- الآن يصبح شريط الحالة نفس لون رأس (الروبوت 5.0+).
- حذف الخيار لتلوين تاب في المحادثات (حتى تتمكن من حل المشكلة).
- مشكلة ثابتة من خيار الاتصالات تسليط الضوء.
- مشكلة ثابتة من خيار لإلغاء تنشيط تقرير التسليم.
- إصلاح أخطاء أخرى.
    </ar>
    <bn>
- সর্বোচ্চ মানের সঙ্গে রাষ্ট্রের মধ্যে ছবি পাঠাতে যোগ করা বিকল্প।
- 5 মিনিট পর্যন্ত রাষ্ট্রের ভিডিওগুলির সময় বাড়ানোর জন্য বিকল্পটি যুক্ত করা হয়েছে (শুধুমাত্র এই বিকল্প সক্রিয় ডিভাইসগুলিতে দৃশ্যমান)।
- এখন স্ট্যাটাসবারের শিরোনাম হিসাবে একই রঙ হয়ে যায় (অ্যান্ড্রয়েড 5.0+)।
- কথোপকথনে ট্যাবটি রঙ করার জন্য মুছে ফেলা বিকল্প (যতক্ষণ না আপনি সমস্যার সমাধান করতে পারেন)।
- হাইলাইট পরিচিতি বিকল্পের স্থায়ী সমস্যা।
- বিতরণ রিপোর্ট নিষ্ক্রিয় করার জন্য স্থির সমস্যা।
- অন্যান্য ত্রুটি সংশোধন
    </bn>
    <de>
- Option um Fotos im Status in der höchsten Qualität einzusetzen.
- Option um die Videolänge des Status auf bis zu 5 Minuten zu erhöhen hinzugefügt (nur sichtbar in Geräten mit dieser Option angezeigt).
- Nun erhält die Statusleiste die selbe Farbe wie die Kopfzeile (Android 5.0+).
- Option zum Färben des Reiters in den Unterhaltungen gelöscht (bis das Problem gelöst werden kann).
- Problem der Kontakte hervorheben Option behoben.
- Problem der Option zum deaktivieren des Zustellberichts behoben.
- Andere Fehler behoben.
	</de>
    <es>
- Añadida opción para mandar fotos en el estado con máxima calidad.
- Añadida opción para aumentar el tiempo de los vídeos del estado, hasta 5 minutos (solo visible en dispositivos con esta opción activa).
- Ahora el statusbar se vuelve del mismo color que el header (Android 5.0+).
- Borrada opción para colorear el TAB en las conversaciones (hasta poder solucionar el problema).
- Solucionado problema de la opción resaltar contatos.
- Solucionado problema de la opción de desactivar el informe de entrega.
- Arreglados otros errores.
    </es>
    <fr>
- Ajout d'une option pour envoyer des photos dans l'état de la plus haute qualité.
- Ajout d'une option pour augmenter le temps des vidéos de l'état, jusqu'à 5 minutes (uniquement visible dans les appareils avec cette option active).
- Maintenant, la barre d'état devient la même couleur que l'en-tête (Android 5.0+).
- Option supprimée pour colorier le TAB dans les conversations (jusqu'à ce que vous puissiez résoudre le problème).
- Correction du problème de l'option contacts en surbrillance.
- Correction du problème de l'option de désactiver le rapport de livraison.
- Correction d'autres erreurs.
    </fr>
    <hi>
- उच्चतम गुणवत्ता के साथ राज्य में तस्वीरें भेजने के लिए विकल्प जोड़ा गया।
- 5 मिनट तक के वीडियो के वीडियो का समय बढ़ाने के लिए विकल्प जोड़ा गया (केवल इस विकल्प के साथ डिवाइस में दृश्यमान सक्रिय)।
- अब स्थितिपट्टी हेडर (एंड्रॉइड 5.0+) के समान ही रंग हो जाती है।
- वार्तालापों में टैब को रंग देने के लिए हटाए गए विकल्प (जब तक आप समस्या हल नहीं कर सकते)।
- हाइलाइट संपर्क विकल्प की फिक्स्ड समस्या
- डिलीवरी रिपोर्ट को निष्क्रिय करने के विकल्प की फिक्स्ड समस्या
- फिक्स्ड अन्य त्रुटियां
- फिक्स्ड अन्य त्रुटियां
    </hi>
    <it>
- Aggiunta opzione per condividere le foto dello stato alla massima qualità.
- Aggiunta opzione per aumentare l'intervallo di tempo dei video nello stato, fino a 5 minuti (visibile solo nei dispositivi che avranno attiva tale opzione).
- Ora la statusbar assume lo stesso colore dell'intestazione (Android 5.0+).
- Eliminata opzione per colorare il pannello nelle conversazioni (fino alla risoluzione del problema).
- Sistemato problema relativo all'opzione di selezione dei contatti.
- Sistemato problema relativo all'opzione per disattivare il rapporto di consegna.
- Sistemati altri errori.
    </it>
    <nl>
- Toegevoegd optie om foto's te sturen in de staat met de hoogste kwaliteit.
- Option toegevoegd om de tijd van de video's van de staat te verhogen, tot 5 minuten (alleen zichtbaar in apparaten met deze optie actief).
- Nu wordt de statusbalk dezelfde kleur als de koptekst (Android 5.0+).
- Verwijderde optie om de TAB in de gesprekken te kleuren (totdat u het probleem kunt oplossen).
- Vast probleem van de hoogtecontact optie.
- Vast probleem met de optie om het leveringsrapport te deactiveren.
- Vaste andere fouten.
    </nl>	
    <pt>
- Adicionada opção para enviar fotos na mais alta qualidade possível. 
- Adicionada opção que aumenta a duração do vídeo no status em até 5 minutos. Porém apenas visível se ativada. 
- Agora a nova barra de status segue a mesma cor que o cabeçalho (Android 5+).
- Removida a opção de colorir a guia de conversas temporariamente. 
- Problema de destacar contatos corrigido. 
- Corrigido o problema em desativar o relatório de entrega. 
- Outros erros corrigidos. 
    </pt>
    <ru>
- Добавлена возможность отправлять фотографии с самым высоким качеством.
- Добавлена опция увеличения времени видео, до 5 минут (видна только в устройствах с активной этой опцией).
- Теперь панель состояния становится того же цвета, что и заголовок (Android 5.0+).
- Удаленная опция для окраски TAB в цепочках (пока мы не можем решить эту проблему).
- Исправлена проблема с опцией подсветки контактов.
- Исправлена проблема с дезактивацией отчета о доставке.
- Исправлены другие ошибки.
    </ru>
    <tr>
- Durum fotoğraflarını en yüksek kalitede gönderme seçeneği eklendi.
- Durum videolarını 5 dakikaya kadar uzatma seçeneği eklendi (sadece seçeneğin aktif olduğu cihazlarda görünür).
- Başlık rengi artık durum çubuğuna uygulanıyor(Android 5.0+).
- Konuşmalarda sekmeleri boyama seçeneği kaldırıldı (sorun çözülene kadar).
- Kişileri vurgulama seçeneği düzeltildi.
- İletildi işaretini gizleme seçeneği düzeltildi.
- Diğer hatalar düzeltildi.
    </tr>
  </update>
</AppUpdater>
