<AppUpdater>
  <update>
    <latestVersion>2.6.5</latestVersion>
    <url>http://dl-xda.xposed.info/modules/kmod.xposed_v2650_287d5e.apk</url>
    <en>
- Added the option to change the floating messages (Toast) with the same appearance as KMod FWA.
- Now when you activate the option "Delete sent messages", you can delete messages of any date.
- Now when the option to hide the last connection is active, the privacy error Toast will not be displayed.
- Optimized the code of privacy options.
- Fixed privacy options.
- Correction of the personalization of the state in conversations.
    </en>
    <ar>
- أضيفت الخيار لتغيير الرسائل العائمة (نخب) مع نفس مظهر كمود فوا.
- الآن عند تفعيل الخيار "حذف الرسائل المرسلة"، يمكنك حذف رسائل من أي تاريخ.
- الآن عندما يكون الخيار لإخفاء آخر اتصال نشط، لن يتم عرض خطأ الخصوصية نخب.
- محسن رمز خيارات الخصوصية.
- خيارات الخصوصية الثابتة.
- تصحيح شخصية الدولة في المحادثات.
    </ar>
    <bn>
- কেমোড এফডব্লুএ হিসাবে একই চেহারা দিয়ে ভাসমান বার্তা (টোস্ট) পরিবর্তন করার বিকল্পটি যুক্ত করেছে।
- এখন আপনি "পাঠানো বার্তাগুলি মুছে ফেলুন" বিকল্পটি সক্রিয় করার সময়, আপনি যেকোনো তারিখের বার্তাগুলি মুছতে পারেন।
- এখন শেষ সংযোগটি গোপন করার সময়টি সক্রিয় থাকলে, গোপনীয়তা ত্রুটিটিউশ প্রদর্শন করা হবে না।
- গোপনীয়তার বিকল্পগুলির কোডটি অপ্টিমাইজ করেছে।
- স্থায়ী গোপনীয়তা অপশন
- কথোপকথন মধ্যে রাষ্ট্র ব্যক্তিগতকরণ সংশোধন।
    </bn>
    <de>
- Option um die schwebenden Benachrichtigungen (Toast) in das selbe Erscheinungsbild wie KMod FWA zu ändern hinzugefügt. 
- Wenn du nun die Option "lösche gesendete Nachrichten" aktivierst, kannst du Nachrichten jeglichen Datums löschen.
- Wenn nun die Option zum verstecken der letzten Verbindung aktiv ist, wird die Privatsphäre Fehler Benachrichtigung nicht angezeigt.
- Code der Privatsphäreoptionen optimiert.
- Privatsphäreoptionen repariert.
- Korrektur der Personalisierung des Status in Unterhaltungen.
	</de>
    <es>
- Añadida la opción para cambiar los mensajes flotantes (Toast) con la misma apariencia que KMod FWA.
- Ahora cuando active la opción "Eliminar mensajes enviados", puede eliminar mensajes de cualquier fecha.
- Ahora cuando está activa la opción de ocultar la última conexión, no se mostrarán los Toast de error de privacidad.
- Optimizado el código de las opciones de privacidad.
- Arregladas opciones de privacidad.
- Corrección de la personalización del estado en conversaciones.
    </es>
    <fr>
- Ajout de l'option pour changer les messages flottants (Toast) avec la même apparence que KMod FWA.
- Maintenant, lorsque vous activez l'option "Supprimer les messages envoyés", vous pouvez supprimer les messages de n'importe quelle date.
- Maintenant, lorsque l'option pour masquer la dernière connexion est active, l'erreur de confidentialité Toast ne sera pas affichée.
- Optimisation du code des options de confidentialité.
- Correction des options de confidentialité.
- Correction de la personnalisation de l'état dans les conversations.
    </fr>
    <hi>
- केमोद एफडब्ल्यूए के रूप में एक ही उपस्थिति के साथ फ्लोटिंग संदेश (टोस्ट) को बदलने के विकल्प को जोड़ा गया
- अब जब आप "भेजे गए संदेश हटाएं" विकल्प सक्रिय करते हैं, तो आप किसी भी तिथि के संदेशों को हटा सकते हैं।
- अब जब अंतिम कनेक्शन को छिपाने का विकल्प सक्रिय है, तो गोपनीयता त्रुटि टोस्ट प्रदर्शित नहीं की जाएगी।
- गोपनीयता विकल्पों का कोड ऑप्टिमाइज़ किया गया
- फिक्स्ड गोपनीयता विकल्प
- वार्तालापों में राज्य के वैयक्तिकरण को सुधारना।
    </hi>
    <it>
- Aggiunta opzione per cambiare i messaggi flottanti (Toast) con lo stesso aspetto di KMod FWA.
- Adesso attivando l'opzione "Cancella messaggi inviati", è possibile cancellare i messaggi di ogni data.
- Adesso quando è attivata l'opzione per nascondere l'ultimo accesso, il messaggio Toast di errore di privacy non verrà visualizzato.
- Ottimizzato il codice delle opzioni di privacy.
- Sistemate opzioni di privacy.
- Correzione della personalizzazione dello stato nelle conversazioni.
    </it>
    <nl>
- De optie toegevoegd om de zwevende berichten (Toast) met dezelfde verschijning als KMod FWA te wijzigen.
- Als u nu de optie "Verwijder verzonden berichten" activeert, kunt u berichten van elke datum verwijderen.
- Als nu de optie om de laatste verbinding te verbergen actief is, wordt de privacyfout Toast niet weergegeven.
- Geoptimaliseerde de code van privacyopties.
- Vaste privacyopties.
- Correctie van de personalisatie van de staat in gesprekken.
    </nl>	
    <pt>
- Adicionada a opção de mudar a mensagem flutuante (Toast) para ficar com a mesma aparência do KMod FWA.
- Quando a opção "Deletar mensagem enviada" for ativada, você poderá deletar mensagens de qualquer data.
- Quando a opção de esconder a ultima conexão for ativada, a mensagem de erro por toast de privacidade não será exibida.
- Otimização no código das opções de privacidade.
- Corrigidos erros das opções de privacidade.
- Correções sobre os estados de personalização nas converças.
    </pt>
    <ru>
- Добавлена возможность изменения плавающих сообщений (Toast) с тем же внешним видом, что и KMod FWA.
- Теперь, когда вы активируете опцию «Удалить отправленные сообщения», вы можете удалять сообщения любой даты.
- Теперь, когда опция скрыть последнее соединение активна, ошибка конфиденциальности Toast не будет отображаться.
- Оптимизирован код параметров конфиденциальности.
- Исправлены параметры конфиденциальности.
- Коррекция персонализации государства в разговорах.
    </ru>
    <tr>
- Toast bildirimlerini KMod FWA ile aynı görünüme sokma ayarı eklendi.
- "Gönderilen mesajları sil" seçeneğini etkinleştirdiğinizde artık tüm mesajları tarih sınırı olmadan silebileceksiniz.
- Artık son görülmeyi gizle seçeneğini etkinleştirdiğinizde, gizlilik hatası bildirimi görüntülenmeyecek.
- Gizlilik ayarlarının kodu optimize edildi.
- Gizlilik ayarları düzeltildi.
- Mesajlaşmalarda durum kişiselleştirmeleri düzeltildi.
    </tr>
  </update>
</AppUpdater>
