<AppUpdater>
  <update>
    <latestVersion>2.7.0</latestVersion>
    <url>https://dl-xda.xposed.info/modules/kmod.xposed_v2700_d797d2.apk</url>
    <en>
- Added whitelist and blacklist for the option, hide reading confirmation.
- Added option to hide you've seen status, with whitelist and blacklist.
- Added icons for the section of the conversation screen.
- Added Romanian language.
- Restructuring of the Screen format of the conversations section.
- Deleted the Delete sent messages option, until the problem is solved.
- Solved interface problems.
    </en>
    <ar>
- تمت إضافة القائمة البيضاء والقائمة السوداء للخيار وإخفاء تأكيد القراءة.
- تمت إضافة خيار لإخفاء حالة المشاهدة ، مع القائمة البيضاء والقائمة السوداء.
- الرموز المضافة لقسم شاشة المحادثة.
- أضيفت اللغة الرومانية.
- إعادة هيكلة تنسيق الشاشة لقسم المحادثات.
- حذف خيار حذف الرسائل المرسلة ، حتى يتم حل المشكلة.
- مشاكل واجهة حلها.
    </ar>
    <bn>
- বিকল্পের জন্য হোয়াইটলিস্ট এবং ব্ল্যাকলিস্ট যোগ করা, পুস্তিকা যাচাইকরণ লুকান
- হোয়াইটলিস্ট এবং ব্ল্যাকলিস্টের সাথে আপনি স্থিতি দেখেছেন, লুকানো বিকল্পটি জুড়েছে।
- কথোপকথন পর্দার অংশ জন্য যোগ করা আইকন।
- রোমান ভাষা যোগ করা হয়েছে
- কথোপকথন বিভাগের স্ক্রিন ফরম্যাটের পুনর্গঠন।
- সমস্যা সমাধান করা হয় না হওয়া পর্যন্ত, পাঠানো বার্তা মুছে ফেলুন মুছে ফেলা।
- সমাধান ইন্টারফেস সমস্যা।
    </bn>
    <de>
- Weiße und Schwarze Liste, für die Option verstecke Lesebestätigung, hinzugefügt.
- Option zum verstecken, dass du den Status gesehen hast, hinzugefügt, mit Weißer und Schwarzer Liste.
- Symbole for den Bereich des Unterhaltungsbildschirms hinzugefügt.
- Rumänische Sprache hinzugefügt.
- Restrukturierung des Bildschirmformats des Unterhaltungsbereich.
- Die lösche gesendete Nachricht Option entfernt, bis das Problem behoben ist, damit es wieder funktioniert.
- Oberflächen Probleme behoben.
	</de>
    <es>
- Se agrego lista blanca y lista negra para la opción, ocultar confirmación de lectura.
- Se agregó la opción para ocultar cuando vea el estado, con lista blanca y lista negra.
- Añadidos iconos para la sección Secciones de la pantalla de conversación.
- Añadido idioma Rumano.
- Restructuración de la sección Formato de pantalla de la sección conversaciones.
- Se eliminó la opción Eliminar mensajes enviados, hasta que se resuelva el problema.
- Arreglados problemas de interfaz.
    </es>
    <fr>
- Ajout de la liste blanche et de la liste noire pour l'option, masquer la confirmation de lecture.
- Ajout de l'option pour masquer vous avez vu le statut, avec liste blanche et liste noire.
- Ajout d'icônes pour la section de l'écran de conversation.
- Ajout de la langue roumaine.
- Restructuration du format écran de la section conversations.
- Suppression de l'option Supprimer les messages envoyés, jusqu'à ce que le problème soit résolu.
- Problèmes d'interface résolus.
    </fr>
    <hi>
- विकल्प के लिए श्वेतसूची और ब्लैकलिस्ट जोड़ा गया, पढ़ने की पुष्टि छुपाएं।
- श्वेतसूची और ब्लैकलिस्ट के साथ, आपको स्थिति को देखने के लिए जोड़ा गया विकल्प जोड़ा गया।
- वार्तालाप स्क्रीन के अनुभाग के लिए जोड़ा गया प्रतीक।
- रोमानियाई भाषा जोड़ा गया।
- वार्तालाप अनुभाग के स्क्रीन प्रारूप का पुनर्गठन।
- समस्या हल होने तक प्रेषित संदेश हटाएं विकल्प हटा दिया गया।
- हल इंटरफ़ेस समस्याएं।
    </hi>
	<in>
- Penambahan daftar putih dan daftar hitam untuk opsi, sembunyikan konfirmasi baca
- Penambahan opsi sembunyi ketika melihat status, dengan daftar putih dan daftar hitam
- Penambahan ikon pada bagian layar percakapan
- Penambahan bahasa Rumania
- Restruktur baru bagian format layar pada bagian percakapan
- Menghilangkan opsi Hapus pesan terkirim, sampai masalah nya diselesaikan sehingga berfungsi kembali
- Penyelesaian masalah antarmuka
	</in>
    <it>
- Aggiunta whitelist e blacklist per le opzioni, opzione per nascondere le conferme di lettura.
- Aggiunta opzione per nascondere la visualizzazione degli stati, con la whitelist e la blacklist.
- Aggiunte icone per la sezione Sezione delle schermate delle conversazioni.
- Aggiunta lingua Rumena.
- Nuova ristrutturazione del formato della schermata della sezione delle conversazioni.
- Eliminate le opzioni per eliminare i messaggi spediti, finchè il problema verrà risolto in modo che possa funzionare nuovamente.
- Risolti problemi di interfaccia.
    </it>
    <nl>
- Toegevoegd witte lijst en zwarte lijst voor de optie, verberg leesbevestiging.
- Optie toegevoegd om te verbergen dat je de status hebt gezien, met witte lijst en zwarte lijst.
- Pictogrammen toegevoegd voor het gedeelte van het gespreksscherm.
- Toegevoegd Roemeense taal.
- Herstructurering van het schermformaat van het gespreksgedeelte.
- De optie Verwijder verzonden berichten verwijderd, totdat het probleem is opgelost.
- Opgeloste interfaceproblemen.
    </nl>	
    <pt>
- Adicionada lista negra e branca para a opção de esconder confirmação de leitura.
- Adicoonada opção para esconder quando você vê o status, com lista branca e negra.
- Adicionados icônes para as seções da tela de conversa.
- Nova lingua disponível, romênio.
- Seçãp de formato de tela foi reestruturada para a seção de conversas.
- Opção de deletar mensagens enviadas desativada até problema ser resolvido nesta.
- Resolvidos problêmas de interface.
    </pt>
	<ro>
- Added whitelist, and blacklist for the option, hide reading confirmation.
- Added option to hide when you see status, with whitelist and blacklist.
- Added icons for the section Sections of the conversation screen.
- Added Romanian language.
- New restructuring of the Screen format section of the conversations section.
- Deleted the Delete sent messages option, until the problem is solved so that it works again.
- Solved interface problems.
	</ro>
    <ru>
- Добавлен белый и черный список для опции, Скрыть подтверждение чтения.
- Добавлена ​​опция скрыть, когда Вы видите статус, со списком белый и черный список.
- Добавлены значки для раздела Разделы экрана беседы.
- Добавлен румынский язык.
- Новая реструктуризация раздела Формат экрана раздела бесед.
- Удалена опция Удалить отправленные сообщения, пока проблема не будет решена, чтобы она снова работала.
- Решенные проблемы с интерфейсом.
    </ru>
    <tr>
-Okundu bilgisini gizleme özelliğine beyaz liste, ve kara liste, özelliği eklendi.
-Durum görüldü bilgisini gizleme, beyaz liste ve kara liste ile, özelliği eklendi.
-Konuşma ekranının Bölümler isimli bölümüne ikonlar eklendi. *added "isimli" because it might be confusing for people*
-Rumence eklendi.
-Konuşmalar bölümünün, ekran düzenleme bölümü yeniden inşa edildi. 
-Gönderilmiş mesajları silme seçeneği problem düzeltilene kadar kaldırıldı.
-Arayüz problemleri düzeltildi.
    </tr>
  </update>
</AppUpdater>
