<AppUpdater>
  <update>
    <latestVersion>2.5.2</latestVersion>
    <url>http://dl-xda.xposed.info/modules/kmod.xposed_v2_9dfc93.apk</url>
    <en>
- Added avatars on screen conversation screen for contacts and groups (Groups will show the group icon, not the contact icon).
- Added option, to make normal calls instead of WhatsApp calls, from the call button on the conversation screen.
- Corrections for the latest beta versions of Google Play.
- Other corrections of errors.
    </en>
	<ar>
- اظهار صور الاشخاص والمجموعات في شاشة المحادثات (المجموعات ستظهر ايقونة المجموعة وليس ايقونة الاسم).
- اضافة خيار لاجراء اتصال عادي من داخل تطبيق الوتساب عن طريق زر الاتصال.
- التصحيح لاخر اصدار بيتا في جوجل بلاي.
- اصلاح اخطاء اخرى.
	</ar>
    <bn>
- পরিচিতি এবং দলের জন্য পর্দা কথোপকথন পর্দায় যোগ করা হয়েছে অবতার (The Groups গ্রুপ আইকন, না পরিচিতি আইকন প্রদর্শন করবে).
- বিকল্প যোগ করা হয়েছে, কথোপকথন পর্দায় কল বোতাম থেকে হোয়াটসঅ্যাপ কলের পরিবর্তে স্বাভাবিক কল করতে.
- গুগল এর সর্বশেষ বিটা সংস্করণ জন্য সংশোধণী খেলুন.
- ত্রুটি অন্যান্য সংশোধন.
    </bn>
    <de>
- Zusätzliche Avatare auf dem Bildschirm Konversation Bildschirm für Kontakte und Gruppen (Gruppen zeigen das Gruppen-Symbol, nicht das Kontakt-Symbol).
- Zusätzliche Option, um normale Anrufe anstelle von WhatsApp-Anrufen von der Anruftaste auf dem Konversationsbildschirm zu machen.
- Korrekturen für die neuesten Beta-Versionen von Google Play.
- Sonstige Fehlerkorrekturen.
    </de>
    <es>
- Añadidos avatares en la pantalla de conversación de la pantalla de contactos y grupos (En grupos se ostrará el icono de grupo, no el icono de contacto).
- Opción agregada, para hacer llamadas normales en lugar de llamadas de WhatsApp, desde el botón de llamada en la pantalla de conversación.
- Correcciones para las últimas versiones beta de Google Play.
- Otras correcciones de errores.
    </es>
    <hi>
- संपर्क और समूह के लिए स्क्रीन बातचीत स्क्रीन पर जोड़ा अवतारों (समूह समूह आइकन, नहीं संपर्क आइकन दिखाई देगा)।
- विकल्प जोड़ा गया है, बातचीत स्क्रीन पर कॉल बटन से, WhatsApp कॉल के बजाय सामान्य कॉल करने के लिए।
- गूगल के नवीनतम बीटा संस्करण के लिए सुधार खेलते हैं।
- त्रुटियों के अन्य सुधार।
    </hi>
    <it>
- Aggiunti gli avatars nella schermata delle conversazioni per contatti e gruppi (per i gruppi verrà mostrato l'avatar del gruppo, non l'avatar del contatto).
- Aggiunta opzione per effettuare una chiamata normale invece di una chiamata WhatsApp, tramite il pulsante di chiamata nella schermata della conversazione.
- Correzioni per le ultime versioni beta del Google Play.
- Altre correzioni di errori.
    </it>
	<nl>
- Toegevoegd, avatars op conversatie scherm voor contacten en groepen (Groepen zal het groeps ikoon te zien zijn en niet het contact ikoon). 
- Optie toegevoegd, om normaal te bellen in plaats van WhatsApp bellen via de bel knop in het conversatie scherm. 
- Correcties voor de laatste beta versies van Google Play. 
- Andere correcties van fouten.
	</nl>	
    <pt>
- Adicionado avatares na tela tela de conversa para contatos e grupos (Grupos mostrará o ícone de grupo, não o ícone de contato).
- Adicionado opção, para fazer chamadas normais em vez de WhatsApp chamadas, a partir do botão de chamada na tela de conversa.
- Correções para as versões beta mais recentes do Google Play.
- Outras correcções de erros.
    </pt>
    <ru>
- Добавлены аватары на экран разговоров, для контактов и групп (будет видна иконка группы, а не контактов)
- Добавлена возможность совершать обычные звонки, вместо звонков WhatsApp. 
- Добавлена поддержка последней бета версии в Google Play. 
- Исправлены прочие ошибки.
    </ru>
    <tr>
- Mesajlaþma ekranýna grup ve kiþiler için profil fotoðraflarý eklendi (Gruplar kiþi yerine grup simgesini gösterir).
- Mesajlaþma ekranýndaki arama tuþuna basýldýðýnda, Whatsapp aramasý yerine normal arama yapma seçeneði eklendi.
- Google Playde'ki son betalar için düzeltmeler.
- DÝðer hata düzeltmeleri.
    </tr>
  </update>
</AppUpdater>
