<AppUpdater>
  <update>
    <latestVersion>2.7.1</latestVersion>
    <url>https://dl-xda.xposed.info/modules/kmod.xposed_v2710_67e3bf.apk</url>
    <en>
- Added option to customize the interface font.
- Added option to disable all tabs (except for chats).
- Now a warning will not be shown when a message has been deleted.
- Fixed option to avoid deleting messages (I was not working correctly on some devices).
- Fixed privacy option, hide recording audio and writing.
- Fixed tab button, now correctly shows the button according to the section.
- Fixed other errors.
    </en>
    <ar>
- وأضاف الخيار لتخصيص خط الواجهة.
- إضافة خيار لتعطيل جميع علامات التبويب (باستثناء الدردشات).
- الآن لن يظهر تحذير عند حذف رسالة.
- خيار ثابت لتجنب حذف الرسائل (لم أكن أعمل بشكل صحيح على بعض الأجهزة).
- خيار الخصوصية الثابتة ، إخفاء تسجيل الصوت والكتابة.
- زر علامة التبويب ثابت ، الآن يظهر بشكل صحيح على الزر وفقا لهذا القسم.
- أخطاء أخرى ثابتة.
    </ar>
    <bn>
- ইন্টারফেস ফন্ট কাস্টমাইজ করার জন্য যোগ করা বিকল্প।
- সব ট্যাব নিষ্ক্রিয় করার জন্য যোগ করা বিকল্প (চ্যাট ছাড়া)।
- একটি বার্তা মুছে ফেলা হয়েছে যখন এখন একটি সতর্কতা দেখানো হবে না।
- বার্তা মুছে ফেলা এড়ানোর জন্য ফিক্সড বিকল্প (আমি কিছু ডিভাইসে সঠিকভাবে কাজ করা হয় নি)
- ফিক্সড গোপনীয়তা বিকল্প, রেকর্ডিং অডিও এবং লেখা লুকান।
- স্থায়ী ট্যাব বোতাম, এখন সঠিকভাবে বিভাগ অনুযায়ী বোতাম দেখায়।
- অন্যান্য ত্রুটি সংশোধন
    </bn>
    <de>
- Option hinzugefügt, um die Schriftart der Benutzeroberfläche anzupassen.
- Option zum deaktivieren aller Tabs (außer Unterhaltungen) hinzugefügt.
- Jetzt wird keine Warnung angezeigt, wenn eine Nachricht gelöscht wurde.
- Option wurde behoben, um das Löschen von Nachrichten zu vermeiden (ich habe auf einigen Geräten nicht richtig funktioniert).
- Privacy-Option behoben, Audio-Aufnahme ausblenden und schreiben.
- Reiter Schaltfläche repariert, es zeigt nun die korrekte Schaltfläche abhängig von der Sektion.
- Andere Fehler behoben.
	</de>
    <es>
- Añadida la opción para personalizar la fuente de la interfaz.
- Añadida la opción para deshabilitar todas las pestañas (excepto la de los chats).
- Ahora no se mostrará una advertencia cuando se haya eliminado un mensaje.
- Arreglada la opción para evitar la eliminación de mensajes (no funcionaba correctamente en algunos dispositivos).
- Arreglada la opción de privacidad, ocultar la grabación de audio y escritura.
- Arreglado el botón de los tabs, ahora muestra correctamente el botón de acuerdo con la sección.
- Se corrigieron otros errores.
    </es>
    <fr>
- Ajout d'une option pour personnaliser la police d'interface.
- Ajout d'une option pour désactiver tous les onglets (sauf pour les chats).
- Maintenant, un avertissement ne sera pas affiché lorsqu'un message a été supprimé.
- Option fixe pour éviter la suppression des messages (je ne travaillais pas correctement sur certains appareils).
- Option de confidentialité fixe, masquer l'enregistrement audio et l'écriture.
- Bouton de tabulation fixe, affiche maintenant correctement le bouton en fonction de la section.
- Correction d'autres erreurs.
    </fr>
    <hi>
- इंटरफेस फ़ॉन्ट को अनुकूलित करने के लिए जोड़ा गया विकल्प।
- सभी टैब अक्षम करने के लिए जोड़ा गया विकल्प (चैट को छोड़कर)।
- जब कोई संदेश हटा दिया गया है तो अब एक चेतावनी दिखाई नहीं देगी।
- संदेशों को हटाने से बचने के लिए निश्चित विकल्प (मैं कुछ उपकरणों पर सही ढंग से काम नहीं कर रहा था)।
- फिक्स्ड गोपनीयता विकल्प, रिकॉर्डिंग ऑडियो और लेखन छुपाएं।
- फिक्स्ड टैब बटन, अब अनुभाग के अनुसार बटन को सही ढंग से दिखाता है।
- अन्य त्रुटियों को फिक्स्ड।
    </hi>
	<in>
- Ditambahkan opsi untuk menyesuaikan font antarmuka.
- Menambahkan opsi untuk menonaktifkan semua tabulasi (kecuali obrolan).
- Sekarang peringatan tidak akan ditampilkan ketika pesan telah dihapus.
- Pilihan tetap untuk menghindari penghapusan pesan (saya tidak bekerja dengan benar pada beberapa perangkat).
- Memperbaiki opsi privasi, menyembunyikan rekaman audio dan menulis.
- Perbaikan tombol tabulasi, kini menampilkan tombol dengan tepat sesuai bagian.
- Perbaikan kerusakan.
	</in>
    <it>
- Aggiunta opzione per personalizzare l'interfaccia del font
- Aggiunta opzione per disabilitare tutti i tab (ad eccezione di quello delle chat).
- Ora non verrà più mostrato un avvertimento quando un messaggio è stato cancellato.
- Risolta opzione per evitare l'eliminazione dei messaggi (non funzionavano correttamente su alcuni dispositivi).
- Risolto il problema della privacy per nascondere la registrazione audio e la scrittura.
- Sistemati pulsanti tab, ora mostrano correttamente il pulsante relativo alla selezione.
- Sistemati altri errori.
    </it>
    <nl>
- Optie toegevoegd om het interfacetype aan te passen.
- Optie toegevoegd om alle tabbladen uit te schakelen (behalve chats).
- Nu wordt er geen waarschuwing weergegeven als een bericht is verwijderd.
- Vaste optie om te voorkomen dat berichten worden verwijderd (op sommige apparaten werkte ik niet correct).
- Vaste privacy-optie, verberg opname-audio en schrijven.
- Vaste tab-knop, geeft nu correct de knop weer volgens de sectie.
- Andere fouten verholpen.
    </nl>	
    <pt>
- Adicionado opção para personalizar a fonte da interface.
- Adicionada a opção de esconder todas as guias, exceto pela de conversas.
- Agora, um aviso não será exibido quando uma mensagem for excluída.
- Opção fixa para evitar a exclusão de mensagens (não estava funcionando corretamente em alguns dispositivos).
- Opção de privacidade fixa, ocultar gravação de áudio e escrita.
- Arrumada a seção de guias, onde agora será mostrada corretamente de acordo com a seção.
- Correção de outros bugs.
    </pt>
	<ro>
- Opțiune adăugată pentru personalizarea fontului interfeței.
- Adăugată opţiunea de a dezactiva toate tab-rile (cu excepţia celor de chat-uri).
- Acum nu va fi afișat un avertisment atunci când un mesaj a fost șters.
- Opțiune fixă pentru a evita ștergerea mesajelor (nu funcționează corect pe unele dispozitive).
- opțiunea de confidențialitate fixă, ascundeți înregistrarea audio și scrierea.
- Butonul tab reparat, acum butonul se afişează corect conform secţiunii.
- S-au rezolvat alte erori .
	</ro>
    <ru>
- Добавлена возможность настройки шрифта интерфейса.
- Добавлена опция отключения всех вкладок (кроме чатов).
- Теперь предупреждение не будет отображаться, когда сообщение было удалено.
- Исправлена возможность избежать удаления сообщений (я не работал правильно на некоторых устройствах).
- Исправлена опция конфиденциальности, скрыть запись звука и запись.
- Исправлена кнопка вкладок, теперь правильно отображается кнопка в соответствии с разделом.
- Исправлены другие ошибки.
    </ru>
    <tr>
- Arabirim yazı tipini özelleştirmek için seçenek eklendi.
- Bütün sekmeleri devre dışı bırakma seçeneği eklendi (konuşmalar hariç)
- Şimdi bir mesaj silindiğinde bir uyarı gösterilmeyecektir.
- Mesajları silmemek için sabit seçenek (Bazı cihazlarda doğru çalışmıyordum).
- Sabit gizlilik seçeneği, kayıt sesini ve yazmayı gizler.
- Sekme butonu düzeltildi, artık bölüme göre doğru butonu gösteriyor.
- Diğer hatalar düzeltildi.
    </tr>
  </update>
</AppUpdater>
