<AppUpdater>
  <update>
    <latestVersion>2.5.7</latestVersion>
    <url>http://dl-xda.xposed.info/modules/kmod.xposed_v2_37cccd.apk</url>
    <en>
- Added load screen for KMod FWA, this screen will display the time it takes to load the application (no extra time).
- Added again the option to hide last connection, but be able to see the connection of your contacts.
- Added icons in the status section.
- Now the Tabs called and states can be hidden independently.
- Added new privacy option, to hide contacts or groups in the list of chats (These will not be seen even when they send you messages.)
- New option of highlighting contacts and groups. Now you can choose up to 8 positions of colors, and in each position, as many contacts or groups as you want.
- Added option to perform searches of contacts or groups, in the two previous options.
- Fixed option to hide Tabs.
- Fixed privacy options.
- Restricted access to Android 7+ until Xposed will be fully functional for Nougat (currently does not work with resources).
- Removed support for versions lower than 2.17.287.
- Deleted section of error log. Now you have to check the errors in the Xposed registry.
- Optimization of the code.
- Fixed other errors.
    </en>
    <ar>
- وأضاف تحميل الشاشة ل كمود فوا، هذه الشاشة سوف يعرض الوقت الذي يستغرقه لتحميل التطبيق (أي وقت إضافي).
- أضيفت مرة أخرى الخيار لإخفاء آخر اتصال، ولكن تكون قادرا على رؤية اتصال جهات الاتصال الخاصة بك.
- أضيفت الرموز في قسم الحالة.
- الآن تابس دعا والدول يمكن أن تكون مخفية بشكل مستقل.
- إضافة خيار الخصوصية الجديدة، لإخفاء جهات الاتصال أو المجموعات في قائمة الدردشات (لن ينظر إلى هذه حتى عندما يرسلون لك رسائل.)
- خيار جديد لتسليط الضوء على الاتصالات والمجموعات. الآن يمكنك اختيار ما يصل إلى 8 مواقف من الألوان، وفي كل موقف، والعديد من الاتصالات أو المجموعات على النحو الذي تريد.
- إضافة خيار لإجراء عمليات البحث من جهات الاتصال أو المجموعات، في الخيارين السابقين.
- الخيار الثابت لإخفاء علامات التبويب.
- خيارات الخصوصية الثابتة.
- تقييد الوصول إلى الروبوت 7+ حتى كبوسد سوف تعمل بكامل طاقتها لنوغات (حاليا لا يعمل مع الموارد).
- إزالة دعم الإصدارات أقل من 2.17.287.
- القسم المحذوف من سجل الأخطاء. الآن لديك للتحقق من الأخطاء في التسجيل كبوسد.
- التحسين من التعليمات البرمجية.
- أخطاء أخرى ثابتة.
    </ar>
    <bn>
- কেমোড FWA- এর জন্য লোড স্ক্রীন যোগ করা হয়েছে, এই পর্দাটি অ্যাপ্লিকেশন (অতিরিক্ত সময়) লোড করতে সময় লাগবে।
- শেষ সংযোগটি আবার গোপন করার জন্য পুনরায় বিকল্পটি যোগ করুন, তবে আপনার পরিচিতিগুলির সংযোগ দেখতে সক্ষম হবেন।
- অবস্থা বিভাগে আইকন যোগ করা হয়েছে
- এখন ট্যাবগুলি বলা হয় এবং স্টেটগুলি স্বাধীনভাবে লুকানো যায়।
- চ্যাটের তালিকায় পরিচিতি বা গোষ্ঠীগুলিকে লুকানোর জন্য নতুন গোপনীয়তা বিকল্প যুক্ত করা হয়েছে (তারা আপনাকে বার্তা পাঠালেও তা দেখা যাবে না।)
- পরিচিতি এবং গ্রুপ হাইলাইট নতুন বিকল্প এখন আপনি রং 8 পদের নির্বাচন করতে পারেন, এবং প্রতিটি অবস্থানে, আপনি চান হিসাবে অনেক পরিচিতি বা গোষ্ঠী হিসাবে।
- দুটি পূর্ববর্তী বিকল্পগুলিতে পরিচিতি বা গোষ্ঠীগুলি অনুসন্ধান করার জন্য যোগ করা বিকল্প।
- ট্যাব আড়াল করার জন্য ফিক্সড বিকল্প
- স্থায়ী গোপনীয়তা অপশন
- Nougat (বর্তমানে সম্পদ সঙ্গে কাজ করে না) জন্য Xposed সম্পূর্ণরূপে কার্যকরী হবে পর্যন্ত অ্যান্ড্রয়েড 7+ থেকে সীমাবদ্ধ অ্যাক্সেস।
- 2.17.287 এর চেয়ে কম সংস্করণগুলির জন্য সরানো সমর্থন
- ত্রুটি লগ এর মুছে ফেলা বিভাগ। এখন আপনি Xposed রেজিস্ট্রি মধ্যে ত্রুটি পরীক্ষা করতে হবে
- কোড অপ্টিমাইজেশান
- অন্যান্য ত্রুটি সংশোধন
    </bn>
    <de>
- Ladebildschirm für KMod FWA hinzugefügt, dieser Bildschirm zeigt an wie viel Zeit benötigt wird die Anwendung zu laden (keine zusätzliche Zeit).
- Option zum verstecken der letzten Verbindung, aber in der Lage zu sein die Verbindungen deiner Kontakte zu sehen, wieder hinzugefügt.
- Symbole im Status Bereich hinzugefügt. 
- Die Reiter Anrufe und Status können nun unabhängig versteckt werden.
- Neue Privatsphärenoption, zum verstecken von Kontakten oder Gruppen in der Liste der Gespräche, hinzugefügt. (Diese sind nicht sichtbar, selbst wenn sie dir Nachrichten zu schicken.)
- Neue Option zum hervorheben von Kontakten und Gruppen. Nun kannst du bis zu 8 Positionen von Farben auswählen und in jeder Position so viele Kontakte oder Gruppen wie du willst.
- Option um Suchen von Kontakten oder Gruppen, in den vorherigen beiden Optionen, zu ermöglichen hinzugefügt.
- Option um Reiter zu verstecken repariert.
- Privatsphäre Optionen repariert.
- Zugriff für Android 7+ verweigert, bis Xposed voll funktional unter Nougat sein wird (derzeit funktionieren Einsatzmittel nicht).
- Unterstützung für Versionen niedriger als 2.17.287 entfernt.
- Fehlerbericht Bereich gelöscht. Nun musst du die Fehler in der Xposed Registrierung überprüfen.
- Optimierungen des Codes.
- Andere Fehler behoben.
	</de>
    <es>
- Añadida pantalla de carga de KMod, esta pantalla se mostrará el tiempo que tarde en cargar la aplicacion (no tiene tiempo extra).
- Añadida de nueva la opción de ocultar última conexión, y poder ver la de la nuestros contactos.
- Addidos iconos en la sección estados.
- Ahora los Tabs llamadas y estados, se pueden ocultar independientemente.
- Añadida nueva opción de privacidad, para ocultar contactos o grupos en la lista de chats (estos no se verán ni cuando nos manden mensajes).
- Nueva opción de resalte de contactos y grupos, hora puedes elegir hasta 8 posiciones de colores, y en cada posición, tantos contactos o grupos como se quiera.
- Añadida opción para poder realizar busquedas de contactos o grupos, en las dos opciones anteriores.
- Arreglada opción de ocultar TABS.
- Arregladas opciones de privacidad.
- Acceso restringido a Android 7+ hasta que Xposed sea totalmente funcional para Nougat (actualmente no funciona con recursos).
- Eliminado el soporte para versiones inferiores a la 2.17.287.
- Eliminada sección del registro de errores. Ahora se consultan los errores en el registro de Xposed.
- Optimización del código.
- Arreglados otros errores.
    </es>
    <fr>
- Ajout d'un écran de chargement pour KMod FWA, cet écran affichera le temps nécessaire pour charger l'application (pas de temps supplémentaire).
- Ajout de l'option de masquer la dernière connexion, mais pouvoir voir la connexion de vos contacts.
- Ajout d'icônes dans la section d'état.
- Maintenant, les onglets appelés et les états peuvent être cachés indépendamment.
- Ajout d'une nouvelle option de confidentialité, pour cacher des contacts ou des groupes dans la liste des chats (ceux-ci ne seront pas visibles même s'ils vous envoient des messages.)
- Nouvelle option pour mettre en évidence les contacts et les groupes. Maintenant, vous pouvez choisir jusqu'à 8 positions de couleurs, et dans chaque position, autant de contacts ou de groupes que vous le souhaitez.
- Ajout d'une option pour effectuer des recherches de contacts ou de groupes, dans les deux options précédentes.
- Correction de l'option pour cacher les onglets.
- Correction des options de confidentialité.
- L'accès restreint à l'Android 7+ jusqu'à Xposed sera entièrement fonctionnel pour le Nougat (actuellement ne fonctionne pas avec les ressources).
- Suppression du support pour les versions inférieures à 2.17.287.
- Section supprimée du journal des erreurs. Maintenant, vous devez vérifier les erreurs dans le registre Xposed.
- Optimisation du code.
- Correction d'autres erreurs.
    </fr>
    <hi>
- केमोड एफडब्ल्यूए के लिए लोड स्क्रीन जोड़ा गया है, यह स्क्रीन एप्लिकेशन को लोड करने में लगने वाला समय प्रदर्शित करेगा (कोई अतिरिक्त समय नहीं)।
- पिछले कनेक्शन को छिपाने का विकल्प फिर से जोड़ा गया, लेकिन अपने संपर्कों का कनेक्शन देखने में सक्षम हो।
- स्थिति अनुभाग में जोड़े गए आइकन।
- अब टैब बुलाए गए और राज्यों को स्वतंत्र रूप से छिपाया जा सकता है
- चैट की सूची में संपर्कों या समूहों को छिपाने के लिए, नई गोपनीयता विकल्प जोड़ा गया (ये आपको संदेश भेजते समय भी नहीं दिखाई देंगे।)
- संपर्कों और समूहों को उजागर करने का नया विकल्प अब आप रंगों की 8 स्थिति तक, और प्रत्येक स्थिति में, जितने चाहें उतने संपर्क या समूह चुन सकते हैं।
- दो पिछले विकल्पों में, संपर्कों या समूहों की खोज करने के लिए जोड़ा विकल्प।
- टैब्स छुपाने के लिए फिक्स्ड विकल्प
- फिक्स्ड गोपनीयता विकल्प
- एंड्रॉइड 7+ तक सीमित पहुंच Xposed तक नोऊगैट (वर्तमान में संसाधनों के साथ काम नहीं करता है) के लिए पूरी तरह कार्यात्मक होगा।
2.17.287 से कम संस्करणों के लिए हटाया गया समर्थन
- त्रुटि लॉग का हटाए गए अनुभाग अब आपको Xposed रजिस्ट्री में त्रुटियों को जांचना होगा।
- कोड का अनुकूलन।
- फिक्स्ड अन्य त्रुटियां
    </hi>
    <it>
- Aggiunta schermata di caricamento per KMod FWA, questa schermata indicherà il tempo necessario per l'avvio dell'applicazione (senza extra tempo aggiuntivo).
- Nuovamente aggiunta l'opzione per nascondere l'ultimo accesso, pur essendo in grado di vedere la connessioni dei propri contatti.
- Aggiunte icone nella sezione Stato
- Ora i pannelli Chiamate e Stato possono essere nascosti indipendentemente.
- Aggiunta nuova opzione privacy, per nascondere contatti e gruppi nella lista delle chat (Questi non saranno visibili neanche se invieranno dei messaggi.)
- Nuova opzione di evidenziazione di contatti e gruppi. Ora è possibile scegliere fino a 8 posizioni di colore, e in ciascuna posizione, quanti contatti e gruppi si desiderano.
- Aggiunta opzione per affinare le ricerche di contatti o gruppi, nelle due precedenti opzioni.
- Sistemata opzione per nascondere i pannelli.
- Sistemate opzioni di privacy.
- Accesso limitato a partire da Android 7+ finchè Xposed non sarà pienamente funzionante per Nougat (momentaneamente non funziona con le sorgenti).
- Rimosso supporto per versioni inferiori a 2.17.287.
- Eliminata sezione per i log di errori. Ora è necessario controllare gli errori nel registro di Xposed.
- Ottimizzazione del codice.
- Sistemati altri errori.
    </it>
    <nl>
- Laad scherm toegevoegd voor KMod FWA, dit scherm geeft de tijd aan die nodig is om de applicatie te laden (geen extra tijd).
- Nog een optie toegevoegd om de laatste verbinding te verbergen, maar de verbinding van uw contacten te kunnen zien.
- Toegevoegde pictogrammen in de status sectie.
- Nu kunnen de tabbladen genaamd en staten onafhankelijk verborgen zijn.
- Nieuwe privacy optie toegevoegd, om contacten of groepen in de lijst met chats te verbergen (deze worden niet gezien, ook wanneer ze berichten naar je verzenden.)
- Nieuwe optie om contacten en groepen te markeren. Nu kunt u tot 8 kleurenposities kiezen, en in elke positie, zoveel contactpersonen of groepen als u wilt.
- Toegevoegde optie om zoekopdrachten van contacten of groepen uit te voeren, in de twee vorige opties.
- Vaste optie om tabbladen te verbergen.
- Vaste privacyopties.
- Beperkte toegang tot Android 7+ tot Xposed zal volledig functioneren voor Nougat (momenteel werkt niet met resources).
- Verwijder ondersteuning voor versies lager dan 2.17.287.
- Verwijderde sectie van foutlogboek. Nu moet u de fouten in het Xposed-register controleren.
- Optimalisatie van de code.
- Vaste andere fouten.
    </nl>	
    <pt>
- Tela de carga adicionada para KMod FWA, esta tela exibirá o tempo necessário para carregar o aplicativo (sem tempo extra).
- Adicionou novamente a opção para esconder a última conexão, mas pode ver a conexão de seus contatos.
- Adicionados ícones na seção de status. 
- Agora as abas de ligações e status podem ser ocultadas separadamente.
- Adicionado nova opção de privacidade, para ocultar contatos ou grupos na lista de bate-papo (Isso não será visto mesmo quando eles lhe enviarem mensagens.)
- Nova opção de destaque de contatos e grupos. Agora você pode escolher até 8 posições de cores, e em cada posição, tantos contatos ou grupos como você deseja.
- Opção adicionada para executar pesquisas de contatos ou grupos, nas duas opções anteriores.
- Opção corrigida para ocultar guias.
- Corrigido opções de privacidade.
- Acesso restrito ao Android 7+ até Xposed será totalmente funcional para Nougat (atualmente não funciona com recursos).
- Suporte removido para versões inferiores a 2.17.287.
- Seção excluída do log de erros. Agora você deve verificar os erros no registro Xposed.
- Otimização do código.
- Corrigido outros erros.
    </pt>
    <ru>
- Добавлен экран загрузки для KMod FWA. Этот экран будет отображаться во время, загрузки приложения.
- Снова добавлена ​​опция скрыть последнее соединение, но у вас будет возможность увидеть соединение ваших контактов.
- Добавлены иконки в разделе статус.
- Теперь вкладки под названием и состояния могут быть скрыты самостоятельно.
- Добавлены новые опции конфиденциальности, чтобы скрыть контакты или группы в списке чатов (они не видны даже, когда они посылают вам сообщения.)
- Новая опция подсветки контактов и групп. Теперь вы можете выбрать до 8 позиций цвета.
- Добавлена возможность выполнять поиск контактов или групп, в предыдущих двух вариантах.
- Исправлена опция для скрытия вкладок.
- Исправлены параметры конфиденциальности.
- Ограниченный доступ к Android 7+ до тех пор, пока Xposed не будет полностью функционировать на Nougat (в настоящее время он не работает с ресурсами).
- Удалена поддержка версий ниже, чем 2.17.287!
- Удаленный раздел журнала ошибок. Теперь вам можно проверить ошибки в реестре Xposed.
- Оптимизация кода.
- Исправлены другие ошибки.
    </ru>
    <tr>
- KMod FWA için yükleme ekranı eklendi, bu ekran uygulamanın yüklenme zamanını gösterecek(yüklemeyi yavaşlatmıyor).
- Son görülmeyi gizleme yeniden eklendi, ayrıca kişilerinizin son görülmesini görebiliyorsunuz.
- Durum bölümüne simgeler eklendi.
- Aramalar ve durumlar sekmeleri artık bağımsız olarak gizlenebiliyor.
- Yeni bir gizlilik seçeneği eklendi, kişi ya da grupları mesajlaşmalardan gizleyebiliyorsunuz (mesaj gönderdiklerinde bildirim alamazsınız).
- Kişi ya da grupları vurgulama eklendi. artık 8 farklı konum seçerek istediğiniz sayıda kişi ya da grubu vurgulaabilirsiniz.
- Kişi ve grupları arama özelliği eklendi, iki önceki ayarlarla birlikte.
- Sekme gizleme sorunları düzeltildi.
- Gizlilik ayarları düzeltildi.
- Nougat üzerinde sorunsuz çalışan Xposed sürümleri bulunana kadar Android 7+ için erişim kısıtlandı (şu anda kaynaklar ile çalışmıyor).
- 2.17.287'den önceki sürümler için destek kaldırıldı.
- Hata kaydı kısmı kaldırıldı, artık hatalara Xposed kayıtlarından bakacaksınız.
- Kod optimizasyonu.
- Diğer hata düzeltmeleri.
    </tr>
  </update>
</AppUpdater>
